[{"filename": "1.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 296, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44082853", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 215, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "10.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 295, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44059829", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 27, "name": "MIN", "long_name": "MIN( long long int a , long long int b)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "10.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 27, "name": "MAX", "long_name": "MAX( long long int a , long long int b)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "10.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 23, "name": "MOD", "long_name": "MOD( long long int x)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "10.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "10.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "100.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43748906", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "100.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1001.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27671346", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "2100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1001.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 38, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1002.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27655473", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "2200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1002.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1003.cpp", "nloc": 59, "token_count": 382, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27629904", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 177, "name": "Programme", "long_name": "Programme()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1003.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( integer argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1003.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1004.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27620595", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "2100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1004.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1005.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27569433", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "2100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1005.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1006.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27541225", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1006.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1006.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1007.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27473419", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "3400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 252, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1007.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1008.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27472897", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1008.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1009.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27472832", "exec_time": "155 ms", "memory": "1300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "1009.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "101.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43748161", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1010.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 349, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27432274", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 324, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1011.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 120, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27398601", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 91, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1011.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1012.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27367780", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1012.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1013.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 108, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27213972", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 82, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1013.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1014.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27211173", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1014.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1015.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 118, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27211098", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 88, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1015.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1016.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 216, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27207771", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 23, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1016.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1017.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27203011", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 119, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1017.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1018.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 111, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27159191", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1018.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1019.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 120, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27155327", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1019.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "102.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43747509", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "102.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1020.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 115, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27155243", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 82, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1020.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1021.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 222, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/27120310", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "3300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1021.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1022.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 460, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26980354", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "2200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 10, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd( int & a)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd( int & a , int & b)", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd( int & a , int & b , int & c)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 19, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd( ll & a)", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 20, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd( ll & a , ll & b)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd( ll & a , ll & b , ll & c)", "start_line": 22, "end_line": 22, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd( double & a)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd( double & a , double & b)", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 24, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd( double & a , double & b , double & c)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 51, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1023.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26954040", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1023.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1024.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26916706", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1024.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1025.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26909161", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 50, "parameters": [], "filename": "1025.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1026.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26807820", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1026.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1027.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26785636", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 18, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1027.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1028.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26783948", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1028.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1029.cpp", "nloc": 59, "token_count": 497, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26589255", "exec_time": "155 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 18, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 42, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const pair<T,S> & v)", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 48, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1029.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1029.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "setmax", "long_name": "setmax( T & _a , T _b)", "start_line": 50, "end_line": 50, "parameters": ["_a", "_b"], "filename": "1029.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "setmin", "long_name": "setmin( T & _a , T _b)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["_a", "_b"], "filename": "1029.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T _a , T _b)", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 52, "parameters": ["_a", "_b"], "filename": "1029.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 56, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1029.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "103.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43747158", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1030.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26494809", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1030.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1031.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26489218", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1031.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1032.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26337159", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "2100 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 209, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1032.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1033.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26293447", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1033.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1034.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26248328", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "tucchiTeam", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1034.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1035.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26248256", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "5200 KB", "usertype": "tucchiTeam", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 247, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1035.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1036.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26235479", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1037.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 289, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26187064", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 256, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1037.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1038.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26165800", "exec_time": "155 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 110, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1038.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1039.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 162, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26153756", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "104.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43745230", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1040.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 334, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/26113128", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 315, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1040.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1041.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 133, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25969285", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1041.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1042.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 132, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25759969", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1042.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1043.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25718372", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "4500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1043.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1044.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25696330", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 225, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1044.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1045.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25695136", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "1045.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 115, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1046.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 343, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25580487", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "8000 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "sa", "long_name": "sa( int x , int y)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1046.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "binp", "long_name": "binp( int x , int y)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1046.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1046.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1047.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 116, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25576324", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 52, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "1047.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1048.cpp", "nloc": 67, "token_count": 364, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25487886", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 18, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 300, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1048.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1049.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 208, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25430197", "exec_time": "249 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1049.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 105, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "105.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 255, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43744732", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 252, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "105.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1050.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25424857", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1050.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1051.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 173, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25353343", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1052.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 282, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25352686", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1052.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1053.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25283762", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "1053.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1054.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25283045", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1054.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1055.cpp", "nloc": 92, "token_count": 473, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25118709", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 22, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 313, "name": "Solution::solve", "long_name": "Solution::solve( std :: istream & in , std :: ostream & out)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 169, "parameters": ["in", "out"], "filename": "1055.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 61, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( std :: istream & in , std :: ostream & out)", "start_line": 179, "end_line": 195, "parameters": ["in", "out"], "filename": "1055.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 41, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 207, "end_line": 233, "parameters": [], "filename": "1055.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1056.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 225, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25109647", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1056.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1057.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25106523", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1057.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1058.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 157, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/755/submission/25099996", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1058.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1059.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 236, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43906288", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "XtraTime", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 87, "name": "calc", "long_name": "calc( ll k)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1059.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll k)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1059.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1059.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "106.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43744155", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "106.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1060.cpp", "nloc": 74, "token_count": 410, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43786108", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 107, "name": "jud", "long_name": "jud( int mid)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "1060.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 259, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 171, "parameters": [], "filename": "1060.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 107, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1061.cpp", "nloc": 77, "token_count": 415, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43785569", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 99, "name": "jud", "long_name": "jud( int mid)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "1061.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 272, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 171, "parameters": [], "filename": "1061.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1062.cpp", "nloc": 98, "token_count": 875, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43779107", "exec_time": "186 ms", "memory": "2700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 16, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 94, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T & x)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( T x)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln( T x)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "write", "long_name": "write( T x)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( T a , T b)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 62, "token_count": 418, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 251, "parameters": [], "filename": "1062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 149, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1063.cpp", "nloc": 78, "token_count": 466, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43721249", "exec_time": "249 ms", "memory": "5700 KB", "usertype": "The", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 23, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 27, "name": "MOD", "long_name": "MOD( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1063.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 68, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "1063.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 30, "name": "logg", "long_name": "logg( ll a)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1063.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 109, "name": "func", "long_name": "func( vector<pair<ll,ll>> A , int k)", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 141, "parameters": ["A", "k"], "filename": "1063.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 217, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 205, "parameters": [], "filename": "1063.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1064.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 316, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43698093", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "2200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 115, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int x)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1064.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 66, "parameters": [], "filename": "1064.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1065.cpp", "nloc": 75, "token_count": 619, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43598323", "exec_time": "171 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 50, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1065.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 57, "name": "MAX", "long_name": "MAX( pair<ll,ll> a1 , pair<ll,ll> a2)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["a1", "a2"], "filename": "1065.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 189, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs( int s , int e , int mid)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["s", "e", "mid"], "filename": "1065.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 169, "parameters": [], "filename": "1065.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1066.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43577521", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 77, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( LL k)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1066.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 105, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1066.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1067.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 387, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43505748", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 56, "token_count": 380, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "1067.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 117, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1068.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43426575", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "2800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 93, "name": "fun", "long_name": "fun( ll k)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1068.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1068.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1069.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 274, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43065019", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 97, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( long long k)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1069.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1069.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "107.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43743655", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "107.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1070.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/43040241", "exec_time": "483 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 186, "name": "binary", "long_name": "binary( long long start , long long end , long long s , long long a [ ] , long long n)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["start", "end", "s", "]", "n"], "filename": "1070.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1070.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1071.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 283, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/42963887", "exec_time": "139 ms", "memory": "1700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 97, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( ll md)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["md"], "filename": "1071.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1071.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1072.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/42722065", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 82, "name": "res", "long_name": "res( int m)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 24, "parameters": ["m"], "filename": "1072.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "1072.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1073.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 287, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/42609876", "exec_time": "233 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 36, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 89, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long k)", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 209, "parameters": [], "filename": "1073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1074.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/42596113", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "2500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1074.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1075.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 297, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/42469028", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 103, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll ind , int n , ll x)", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["ind", "n", "x"], "filename": "1075.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 68, "name": "lower_bound", "long_name": "lower_bound( int n , ll x)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["n", "x"], "filename": "1075.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 76, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 40, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1075.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1077.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 301, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/42318005", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "file", "long_name": "file()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "1077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 91, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( int m)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["m"], "filename": "1077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 102, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1079.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 328, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/42285775", "exec_time": "139 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 135, "name": "func", "long_name": "func( long long int a [ ] , long long int n , long long int k)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["]", "n", "k"], "filename": "1079.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1079.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "108.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43740908", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "108.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1080.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 357, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/42281443", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 44, "name": "moha", "long_name": "moha()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1080.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( ll x)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1080.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "1080.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1081.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 334, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/41652768", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 96, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( ll mid)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "1081.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "1081.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1082.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/41582724", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 82, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int m)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["m"], "filename": "1082.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1082.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1083.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 258, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/41396343", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "2900 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 106, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( long long p)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "1083.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1083.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1084.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 241, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/812/submission/39187108", "exec_time": "217 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 99, "name": "func", "long_name": "func( int k)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1084.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1084.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1085.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 402, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/44093349", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 26, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 79, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( ll ma)", "start_line": 58, "end_line": 80, "parameters": ["ma"], "filename": "1085.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 82, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1085.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1086.cpp", "nloc": 89, "token_count": 533, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/44090372", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "40100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 9, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "stringToInteger", "long_name": "stringToInteger( string x)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 64, "name": "powmod", "long_name": "powmod( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "1086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 18, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 66, "name": "mulmod", "long_name": "mulmod( ll a , ll b , ll m)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "1086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 85, "name": "pow", "long_name": "pow( ll a , ll b , ll MOD)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD"], "filename": "1086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "InverseEuler", "long_name": "InverseEuler( ll n , ll MOD)", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["n", "MOD"], "filename": "1086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 51, "name": "C", "long_name": "C( ll n , ll r , ll MOD)", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 143, "parameters": ["n", "r", "MOD"], "filename": "1086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 83, "name": "is", "long_name": "is( ll m)", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 187, "parameters": ["m"], "filename": "1086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 67, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 189, "end_line": 217, "parameters": [], "filename": "1086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1087.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/44084128", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 69, "name": "predicate", "long_name": "predicate( long long int n , long long int k)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "1087.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1087.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1088.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/44076784", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 64, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long k , long long n)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["k", "n"], "filename": "1088.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1088.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1089.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/44060994", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 74, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long k)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1089.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 69, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1089.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "109.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43738539", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1090.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/44024480", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 60, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( long long int n , long long int mid)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["n", "mid"], "filename": "1090.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 118, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1090.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1091.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/44024538", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 60, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( long long int n , long long int mid)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["n", "mid"], "filename": "1091.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 118, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1091.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1092.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/44024444", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 64, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long k , long long n)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["k", "n"], "filename": "1092.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1092.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1093.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43924041", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 78, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll k)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1093.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1093.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1094.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43905815", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 64, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long k , long long n)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["k", "n"], "filename": "1094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1095.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43905886", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 88, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( long long k)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1096.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 160, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43824475", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 65, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll k , ll n)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["k", "n"], "filename": "1096.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1096.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1097.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 161, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43821099", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 63, "name": "calcan", "long_name": "calcan( long long int n , long long int k)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "1097.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 88, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1097.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1098.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43820050", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 123, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 19, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "1098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1099.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43813370", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 78, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( UINT64 n , UINT64 k)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "1099.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 91, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , const char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1099.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "11.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44056232", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 145, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "11.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "110.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 332, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43737009", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 65, "name": "fast_exp", "long_name": "fast_exp( llp base , llp exp , llp m)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["base", "exp", "m"], "filename": "110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 205, "end_line": 261, "parameters": [], "filename": "110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1100.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43803576", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 63, "name": "fun", "long_name": "fun( ll n , ll k)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "1100.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1100.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1101.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43791813", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 81, "name": "fun", "long_name": "fun( ll k , ll n)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["k", "n"], "filename": "1101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1102.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 133, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43788259", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 110, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1102.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1103.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 276, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43600162", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "117500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1104.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43571068", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 59, "name": "good", "long_name": "good( long long m)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["m"], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 70, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1105.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43557125", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 61, "name": "Will_eat_half", "long_name": "Will_eat_half( long long k , long long n)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["k", "n"], "filename": "1105.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 61, "name": "My_binary_search", "long_name": "My_binary_search( long long n)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1105.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 39, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1105.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1106.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43520991", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 55, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long k)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 14, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1106.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 66, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "1106.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1107.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 211, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43503041", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 95, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long cur)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["cur"], "filename": "1107.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1107.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1108.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43492065", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 78, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long m)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["m"], "filename": "1108.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 91, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1108.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1109.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43460856", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "111.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 287, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43736436", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 276, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "111.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1110.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43452629", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 54, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int64 val , int64 n)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["val", "n"], "filename": "1110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1111.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 273, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43419592", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 88, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( ll int k , ll int n)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["k", "n"], "filename": "1111.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1111.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1112.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43412749", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 84, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll i , ll n)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["i", "n"], "filename": "1112.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 118, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1112.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1113.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43357776", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 85, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x , ll k)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["x", "k"], "filename": "1113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 73, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1114.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43341164", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "KonkurBeChapChap", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1114.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1115.cpp", "nloc": 89, "token_count": 466, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43270273", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 42, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 33, "name": "sod", "long_name": "sod( ll n)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 78, "name": "dfs", "long_name": "dfs( graph & g , int visited [ ] , int start)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["g", "]", "start"], "filename": "1115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 46, "name": "bit_getsum", "long_name": "bit_getsum( ll bit [ ] , ll index)", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["]", "index"], "filename": "1115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 44, "name": "bit_update", "long_name": "bit_update( ll bit [ ] , int n , ll index , ll v)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["]", "n", "index", "v"], "filename": "1115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 127, "end_line": 199, "parameters": [], "filename": "1115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1116.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43172280", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 85, "name": "can", "long_name": "can( long long u)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["u"], "filename": "1116.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 66, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs( long long l , long long r)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1116.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1116.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1117.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 205, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43171799", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 85, "name": "can", "long_name": "can( long long u)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["u"], "filename": "1117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 66, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs( long long l , long long r)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1118.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 266, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43170816", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 63, "name": "Solution::check", "long_name": "Solution::check( ll k)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1118.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 60, "name": "Solution::get", "long_name": "Solution::get( ll _N)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["_N"], "filename": "1118.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "_main", "long_name": "_main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1118.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 41, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1118.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1119.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43167547", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 187, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1119.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 45, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "1119.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "112.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43736298", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "112.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1120.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43160704", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "President", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 57, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long k)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 60, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 14, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1121.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 165, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43064664", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 57, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1122.cpp", "nloc": 89, "token_count": 495, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43029902", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "aryanc-403", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 31, "name": "aryanc403", "long_name": "aryanc403()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "1122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 20, "name": "CMP::operator ( )", "long_name": "CMP::operator ( )( lli a , lli b)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 137, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 63, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( map<lli,lli> & m , lli x)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["m", "x"], "filename": "1122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 56, "name": "del", "long_name": "del( map<lli,lli> & m , lli x)", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 171, "parameters": ["m", "x"], "filename": "1122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 41, "name": "cmp", "long_name": "cmp( const ii & a , const ii & b)", "start_line": 175, "end_line": 181, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 82, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( lli n , lli k)", "start_line": 201, "end_line": 249, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "1122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 95, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 253, "end_line": 295, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1123.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43014556", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 64, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( long long n , long long a)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["n", "a"], "filename": "1123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1124.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 146, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43013121", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 65, "name": "Can", "long_name": "Can( long long T , long long K)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["T", "K"], "filename": "1124.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 69, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1124.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1125.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/43005299", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 81, "name": "func", "long_name": "func( ll k , ll n)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 28, "parameters": ["k", "n"], "filename": "1125.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 80, "name": "bin_search", "long_name": "bin_search( ll n)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 52, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1125.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 54, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1125.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1126.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42900290", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 66, "name": "cando", "long_name": "cando( long long k)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 77, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "1126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1127.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42886362", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 83, "name": "ceater", "long_name": "ceater( long long int n , long long int z)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["n", "z"], "filename": "1127.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1127.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1128.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 239, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42871864", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 81, "name": "eat", "long_name": "eat( ll k)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1128.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1128.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1129.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42871823", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 63, "name": "eat", "long_name": "eat( ll k)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1129.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1129.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "113.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43732651", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 202, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1130.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42870456", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 58, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll n , ll p)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["n", "p"], "filename": "1130.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 77, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1130.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1131.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 314, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42862707", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 20, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "1131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "1131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 64, "parameters": [], "filename": "1131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1132.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42830069", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 127, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll st , ll end)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["st", "end"], "filename": "1132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 37, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1133.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42819694", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 70, "name": "isPos", "long_name": "isPos( long long int n , long long int val)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["n", "val"], "filename": "1133.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 74, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1133.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1134.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42804063", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 64, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long n , long long k)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "1134.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1134.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1135.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42743493", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 70, "name": "valid", "long_name": "valid( ll k)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 73, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1136.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42549376", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Test", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 76, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1136.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 74, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( llint n , llint num)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["n", "num"], "filename": "1136.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1137.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42548685", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Test", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 100, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long k)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1137.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , const char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1137.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1138.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42547232", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 70, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( ll k)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 63, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1139.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42467030", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1139.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "114.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43732127", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "114.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1140.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42461996", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 85, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( long long m)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["m"], "filename": "1140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1141.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 227, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42455146", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 18, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 63, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( LL mid)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "1141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 98, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1142.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42436521", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 22, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "1142.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1143.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42428523", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 63, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll i)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["i"], "filename": "1143.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 75, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1143.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1144.cpp", "nloc": 73, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42344454", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 96, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll n , ll k)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "1144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 77, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 153, "parameters": [], "filename": "1144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 45, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 181, "parameters": [], "filename": "1144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1145.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 217, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42341816", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 67, "name": "pred", "long_name": "pred( ll n , ll k)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "1145.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1145.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1146.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42317402", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1146.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1147.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42307139", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 192, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1147.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 22, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "1147.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1148.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 166, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42275306", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 65, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll x)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1148.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 78, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1148.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1149.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 382, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42273300", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "1149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "1149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 108, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll mid , ll n , ll t)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["mid", "n", "t"], "filename": "1149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 161, "parameters": [], "filename": "1149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "115.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43729344", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 37, "name": "count", "long_name": "count( ll n)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1150.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 465, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/991/submission/42269911", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 50, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const vector<T> & t)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["os", "t"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 55, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const array<T,n> & t)", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 14, "parameters": ["os", "t"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 42, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const pair<S,T> & t)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["os", "t"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "MX", "long_name": "MX( T & l , const T & r)", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 16, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "MN", "long_name": "MN( T & l , const T & r)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 44, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 112, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1151.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44089134", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 87, "name": "ch", "long_name": "ch( ll mid)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "1151.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "1151.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1152.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 160, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44088821", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1152.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1153.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44056880", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1154.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 110, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44042960", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 91, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "1154.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1155.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44038202", "exec_time": "233 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1155.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1156.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44030658", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char ** argv)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["argc", "argv"], "filename": "1156.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1157.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 264, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/44018274", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "1157.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1158.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 290, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43800830", "exec_time": "295 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 283, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 205, "parameters": [], "filename": "1158.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 193, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1159.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43799367", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 64, "name": "pred", "long_name": "pred( int mid)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "1159.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1159.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "116.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43727424", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "116.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1160.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43669410", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1161.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43532007", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 24, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 205, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1161.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1162.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 296, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43528796", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 54, "parameters": [], "filename": "1162.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1163.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43524256", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1163.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1164.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 316, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43517990", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 44, "end_line": 68, "parameters": [], "filename": "1164.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1165.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43181414", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1165.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1166.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43163959", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 24, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "1166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1167.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43070925", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1167.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1168.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 501, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/43031844", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "11500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 23, "name": "judge", "long_name": "judge()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "1168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 68, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "1168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 111, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T & x)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 36, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( char c)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["c"], "filename": "1168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 86, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( T x)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "flush", "long_name": "flush()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "1168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1169.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 818, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42915476", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 20, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 30, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "to_string", "long_name": "to_string( string s)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "to_string", "long_name": "to_string( char c)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["c"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "to_string", "long_name": "to_string( const char * s)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "to_string", "long_name": "to_string( bool b)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["b"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 33, "name": "to_string", "long_name": "to_string( pair<A,B> p)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["p"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 55, "name": "to_string", "long_name": "to_string( A v)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "debug_out", "long_name": "debug_out()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "debug_out", "long_name": "debug_out( Head H , Tail ... T)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["H", "T"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "to_str", "long_name": "to_str( const int & n)", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "to_str", "long_name": "to_str( const ll & n)", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "tostring", "long_name": "tostring( T x , int len = 0)", "start_line": 121, "end_line": 121, "parameters": ["x", "0"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "convert", "long_name": "convert( string x , T & r)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["x", "r"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "powmod", "long_name": "powmod( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 125, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "modinv", "long_name": "modinv( ll a)", "start_line": 127, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "modinv", "long_name": "modinv( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 129, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 83, "name": "nCkMp", "long_name": "nCkMp( ll n , ll k)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 121, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 175, "parameters": [], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 26, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 179, "end_line": 187, "parameters": [], "filename": "1169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "117.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43723838", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1170.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42908931", "exec_time": "217 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1171.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42860740", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 18, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "1171.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1172.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42826267", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1173.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42801984", "exec_time": "233 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1173.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1174.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 281, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42799907", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 68, "name": "modPow", "long_name": "modPow( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "1174.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 167, "parameters": [], "filename": "1174.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 115, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1176.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 113, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42759111", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1176.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1177.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 249, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42734251", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 97, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( Drake & x)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1177.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1177.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1178.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42733486", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1178.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1179.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 313, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42710516", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 42, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1179.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "compare", "long_name": "compare( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1179.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 21, "name": "compare_str", "long_name": "compare_str( string s1 , string s2)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["s1", "s2"], "filename": "1179.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 62, "name": "dfs", "long_name": "dfs( vc<vc<ll>> & graph , vc<bool> & visited , ll v)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["graph", "visited", "v"], "filename": "1179.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1179.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "118.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43723340", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "118.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1180.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42696807", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "1180.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1181.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 243, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42678608", "exec_time": "77 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1181.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1182.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 123, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42646393", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 102, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1182.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1183.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 275, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42545871", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "39100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 26, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 19, "name": "in", "long_name": "in()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 19, "name": "Lin", "long_name": "Lin()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 19, "name": "Din", "long_name": "Din()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "1183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 50, "name": "two", "long_name": "two( int n , int val)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["n", "val"], "filename": "1183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 78, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs( int n)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 141, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 50, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 159, "parameters": [], "filename": "1183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1184.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42479180", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1184.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1185.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 243, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42471137", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 22, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 68, "parameters": [], "filename": "1185.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1186.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 138, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42435509", "exec_time": "295 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1186.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1187.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42417326", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1187.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1188.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 131, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42346958", "exec_time": "935 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "ays", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 118, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1188.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1189.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42336345", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1189.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "119.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 231, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43722164", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "119.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1190.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 93, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42331313", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1190.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1191.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42319706", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 32, "name": "input", "long_name": "input()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 19, "parameters": [], "filename": "1191.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 67, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "1191.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 47, "name": "output", "long_name": "output()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1191.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 20, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1191.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1192.cpp", "nloc": 63, "token_count": 430, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42317057", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 21, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "amin", "long_name": "amin( T & x , U y)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "amax", "long_name": "amax( T & x , U y)", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 48, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 56, "name": "operator <", "long_name": "operator <( const Edge & e , const Edge & f)", "start_line": 56, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["e", "f"], "filename": "1192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 66, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1193.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42312902", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "1193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1194.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 142, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42311495", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 135, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "1194.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1195.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 267, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42305225", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 193, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "1195.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1196.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42298448", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1196.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1197.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42263375", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 187, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1197.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 45, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1197.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1198.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42263207", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1198.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1199.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 166, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42248383", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1199.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "12.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44052493", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "12.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "120.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43719839", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1200.cpp", "nloc": 116, "token_count": 810, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42207768", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "brotechies", "function_count": 16, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 37, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 19, "name": "Int", "long_name": "Int()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 19, "name": "Long", "long_name": "Long()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "Char", "long_name": "Char( char * ch)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["ch"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 20, "name": "abs", "long_name": "abs( t a)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 58, "name": "modpow", "long_name": "modpow( T b , T p , T Mod)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["b", "p", "Mod"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "ModInv", "long_name": "ModInv( T b , T Mod)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["b", "Mod"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 45, "name": "pwr", "long_name": "pwr( T b , T p)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["b", "p"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 91, "name": "Int", "long_name": "Int( T & n)", "start_line": 127, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "Int", "long_name": "Int( T & a , U & b)", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 28, "name": "Int", "long_name": "Int( T & a , U & b , W & c)", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 163, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 34, "name": "Int", "long_name": "Int( T & a , U & b , W & c , X & d)", "start_line": 165, "end_line": 171, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c", "d"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "swap", "long_name": "swap( T & a , U & b)", "start_line": 173, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 54, "name": "Unique", "long_name": "Unique( vector<int> v)", "start_line": 175, "end_line": 183, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 51, "name": "split", "long_name": "split( const string & s , char c)", "start_line": 185, "end_line": 199, "parameters": ["s", "c"], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 293, "end_line": 345, "parameters": [], "filename": "1200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1201.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42207742", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "brotechies", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1201.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1202.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 324, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42112183", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "3500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 45, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "deb", "long_name": "deb( istream_iterator<string> it)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "1202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 41, "name": "deb", "long_name": "deb( istream_iterator<string> it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "1202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "tostr", "long_name": "tostr( int n)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 18, "name": "Fuck::Fuck", "long_name": "Fuck::Fuck( ll _x , int _id)", "start_line": 169, "end_line": 175, "parameters": ["_x", "_id"], "filename": "1202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 18, "name": "Fuck::operator <", "long_name": "Fuck::operator <( const Fuck & f) const", "start_line": 177, "end_line": 181, "parameters": ["f"], "filename": "1202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "dist", "long_name": "dist( int x , int y)", "start_line": 185, "end_line": 193, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 195, "end_line": 219, "parameters": [], "filename": "1202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1203.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42086733", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1204.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 142, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/42011630", "exec_time": "920 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "1204.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1205.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41994273", "exec_time": "249 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 18, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1205.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1206.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41987754", "exec_time": "935 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "1206.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1207.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41980697", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1208.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 249, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41957541", "exec_time": "249 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "lowbit", "long_name": "lowbit( int x)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1209.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41948314", "exec_time": "264 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "1209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "121.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43717707", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1210.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 355, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41911198", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 25, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 31, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll int a , ll int b)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 64, "name": "fast_power", "long_name": "fast_power( ll int base , ll int power , ll int mod)", "start_line": 44, "end_line": 54, "parameters": ["base", "power", "mod"], "filename": "1210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 107, "name": "scan", "long_name": "scan()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 72, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1211.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41749247", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1211.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1212.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41724036", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1213.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41670589", "exec_time": "233 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1214.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41654835", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1216.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 239, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41649876", "exec_time": "217 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 224, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "1216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1217.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41638079", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1217.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1218.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41637401", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 135, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1218.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1219.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41601616", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1219.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "122.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43716368", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1220.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41599167", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 20, "parameters": [], "filename": "1220.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1221.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41589669", "exec_time": "592 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 83, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 16, "parameters": [], "filename": "1221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "1221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1222.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41589513", "exec_time": "592 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 83, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 15, "parameters": [], "filename": "1222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1223.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 129, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41571065", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "1223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1224.cpp", "nloc": 83, "token_count": 469, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41469845", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 63, "name": "itosm", "long_name": "itosm( ll x)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 67, "name": "stoim", "long_name": "stoim( string str)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["str"], "filename": "1224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 59, "name": "binpow", "long_name": "binpow( ll x , ll st)", "start_line": 121, "end_line": 137, "parameters": ["x", "st"], "filename": "1224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 122, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 187, "parameters": [], "filename": "1224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 36, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 191, "end_line": 243, "parameters": [], "filename": "1224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1225.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41433093", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1226.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41334535", "exec_time": "249 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1226.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1227.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 216, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41319319", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "15700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1227.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1228.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41308941", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1228.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1229.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 145, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41291000", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1229.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "123.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43715749", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 23, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( double a , double b)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1230.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41274791", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 17, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1230.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 105, "name": "run", "long_name": "run()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1230.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 12, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1230.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1231.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 138, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41264866", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1231.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1232.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41258247", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1233.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41253378", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "1233.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1234.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41243618", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1234.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1235.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41210550", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "1500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 33, "name": "compare", "long_name": "compare( const pair<int,int> & a , const pair<int,int> & b)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1236.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41200047", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1237.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41150886", "exec_time": "233 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1237.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1238.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 290, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41146969", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 193, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1238.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1239.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 112, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41098603", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 105, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "1239.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "124.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 361, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43713128", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 354, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "124.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1240.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 160, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/41085154", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1240.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1241.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40996735", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 217, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1241.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1242.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 222, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40996717", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 215, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1242.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1243.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40996633", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 211, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "1243.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1244.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40881323", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "1244.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1245.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 312, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40843327", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 117, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int val)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["val"], "filename": "1245.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1245.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1246.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40774815", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "1246.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1247.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 120, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40728166", "exec_time": "858 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "HuNau", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 105, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1247.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1248.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 173, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40695941", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "black_phoenix", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1248.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1249.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 129, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40682115", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "125.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43712509", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "125.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1250.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40655509", "exec_time": "217 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1250.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1251.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 232, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40646551", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1251.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 32, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1252.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40631974", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1252.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1253.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 238, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40619343", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 205, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1253.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1254.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40604213", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1255.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 685, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40564003", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 12, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 8, "name": "_iter_wrapper::begin", "long_name": "_iter_wrapper::begin()", "start_line": 1, "end_line": 1, "parameters": [], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 8, "name": "_iter_wrapper::end", "long_name": "_iter_wrapper::end()", "start_line": 1, "end_line": 1, "parameters": [], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 27, "name": "span", "long_name": "span( const T * arr , int n)", "start_line": 2, "end_line": 3, "parameters": ["arr", "n"], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "span", "long_name": "span( const T(&arr) [ N ])", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 3, "parameters": ["]"], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 42, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( T & out , V val)", "start_line": 22, "end_line": 23, "parameters": ["out", "val"], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 48, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( T & out , V val)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 24, "parameters": ["out", "val"], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 66, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( T & out , V val)", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["out", "val"], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 6, "name": "DD", "long_name": "DD( ...)", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["..."], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 119, "name": "DD", "long_name": "DD( const char * format , T elem , S ... rest)", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["format", "elem", "rest"], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 64, "name": "_printDebug", "long_name": "_printDebug( int line , const char * format , T ... elems)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["line", "format", "elems"], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 37, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 88, "name": "run", "long_name": "run()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "1255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1256.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 104, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40528866", "exec_time": "233 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 90, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 19, "parameters": [], "filename": "1256.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1257.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40502076", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "1257.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1258.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 128, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40460879", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1259.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40390182", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1259.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "126.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43704864", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1260.cpp", "nloc": 61, "token_count": 401, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40360726", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 95, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( int & v)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1260.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "1260.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1261.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40314727", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1261.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1262.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 514, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40241139", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 37, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "1262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 84, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T & res)", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["res"], "filename": "1262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T1 & r1 , T2 & r2)", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 159, "parameters": ["r1", "r2"], "filename": "1262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T1 & r1 , T2 & r2 , T3 & r3)", "start_line": 161, "end_line": 161, "parameters": ["r1", "r2", "r3"], "filename": "1262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 38, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const pair<T1,T2> & p)", "start_line": 169, "end_line": 169, "parameters": ["os", "p"], "filename": "1262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 55, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 171, "end_line": 171, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 179, "end_line": 227, "parameters": [], "filename": "1262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1263.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 160, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40231817", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 145, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1263.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1264.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40223038", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1265.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40202195", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1265.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1266.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40195849", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 16, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 18, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 121, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "1266.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 61, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 169, "end_line": 209, "parameters": [], "filename": "1266.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1267.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40177370", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1267.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1268.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 253, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40170348", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "_dbg", "long_name": "_dbg( const char * sdbg , TH h)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["sdbg", "h"], "filename": "1268.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 51, "name": "_dbg", "long_name": "_dbg( const char * sdbg , TH h , TA ... a)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["sdbg", "h", "a"], "filename": "1268.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1268.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1269.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40168268", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 43, "name": "lgput", "long_name": "lgput( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1269.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1269.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "127.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43704712", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "127.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1270.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 338, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40099087", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "scf", "long_name": "scf( int & x)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "scf", "long_name": "scf( ll & x)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "scf", "long_name": "scf( ull & x)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "scf", "long_name": "scf( double & x)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "scf", "long_name": "scf( char & x)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "scf", "long_name": "scf( char * x)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 124, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1271.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 329, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40091421", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 106, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1271.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 53, "name": "rt", "long_name": "rt( ll x)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1271.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 32, "name": "upd", "long_name": "upd( int & x , int y)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1271.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1271.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1272.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 137, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40086121", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1272.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1273.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 122, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40069789", "exec_time": "217 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 106, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1273.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1274.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 140, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40065310", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 119, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "1274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1275.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 125, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40057769", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 118, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1275.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1276.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40057606", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 54, "name": "rd", "long_name": "rd( T & x)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 21, "name": "ceiling", "long_name": "ceiling( int a , int b)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 88, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1277.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 113, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/40026900", "exec_time": "608 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 92, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1277.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1278.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 689, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39965585", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T m , T n)", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["m", "n"], "filename": "1278.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 110, "name": "exgcd", "long_name": "exgcd( T a , T b , T & sa , T & ta)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 19, "parameters": ["a", "b", "sa", "ta"], "filename": "1278.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 88, "name": "mul_inv", "long_name": "mul_inv( T a , T b)", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 20, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1278.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 64, "name": "powmod", "long_name": "powmod( T a , T b , T MOD)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD"], "filename": "1278.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "_dbg", "long_name": "_dbg( const char * sdbg , TH h)", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 34, "parameters": ["sdbg", "h"], "filename": "1278.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 51, "name": "_dbg", "long_name": "_dbg( const char * sdbg , TH h , TA ... t)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["sdbg", "h", "t"], "filename": "1278.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1278.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1279.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39959143", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "1279.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "128.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 532, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43704266", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 514, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "128.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1280.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 91, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39947157", "exec_time": "233 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "1280.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1281.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39944195", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 91, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "1281.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1281.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1282.cpp", "nloc": 13, "token_count": 102, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39941185", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 95, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "1282.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1284.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39939588", "exec_time": "249 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "us", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1284.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1285.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 127, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39863174", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 95, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "1285.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1287.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39857495", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1287.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1289.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39817598", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1289.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "129.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43702784", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "129.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1290.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 125, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39816609", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "de", "long_name": "de( int x , int y)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 5, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1290.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1290.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1291.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 273, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39796604", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 146, "name": "source", "long_name": "source()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 139, "parameters": [], "filename": "1291.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 42, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 169, "parameters": [], "filename": "1291.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1292.cpp", "nloc": 74, "token_count": 411, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39781172", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "11800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 78, "name": "SieveOfErat", "long_name": "SieveOfErat()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1292.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 32, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll aa , ll id2)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["aa", "id2"], "filename": "1292.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 242, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 189, "parameters": [], "filename": "1292.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1293.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39775947", "exec_time": "217 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1293.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1294.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39766265", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1294.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1295.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39758498", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Legendary", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "amin", "long_name": "amin( T & x , U y)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 5, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1295.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1295.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1296.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39753107", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "1296.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1297.cpp", "nloc": 75, "token_count": 889, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39744579", "exec_time": "202 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 13, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "is_vowel", "long_name": "is_vowel( char c)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["c"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 44, "name": "getDistance", "long_name": "getDistance( ld x1 , ld y1 , ld x2 , ld y2)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 66, "name": "extended_euclidean", "long_name": "extended_euclidean( ll a , ll b , ll & x , ll & y)", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 63, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll base , ll p)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 91, "parameters": ["base", "p"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "vec", "long_name": "vec( ii a , ii b)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 53, "name": "getArea", "long_name": "getArea( ii a , ii b , ii c)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 197, "name": "luckyCnt", "long_name": "luckyCnt( int idx , bool x , bool y , bool is)", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["idx", "x", "y", "is"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 44, "name": "zbt", "long_name": "zbt( int a , int b)", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 145, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 37, "name": "islucky", "long_name": "islucky( int a)", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 159, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 10, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int start , int fini)", "start_line": 161, "end_line": 165, "parameters": ["start", "fini"], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 169, "end_line": 219, "parameters": [], "filename": "1297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1298.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39731957", "exec_time": "61 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 124, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "1298.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1299.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/996/submission/39703680", "exec_time": "234 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1299.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "13.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44047855", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "13.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "130.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43702243", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "130.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1300.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44099663", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 25, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 113, "name": "possible", "long_name": "possible( ll x)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 52, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 78, "parameters": [], "filename": "1300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1301.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 364, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44082694", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 327, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1301.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1302.cpp", "nloc": 156, "token_count": 749, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44075890", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 185, "name": "ha", "long_name": "ha()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1302.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 153, "name": "ch", "long_name": "ch( ll wgh)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 143, "parameters": ["wgh"], "filename": "1302.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 94, "token_count": 361, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 331, "parameters": [], "filename": "1302.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 187, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1303.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 351, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44036949", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 262, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 149, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1303.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1304.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 313, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44034887", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 32, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 81, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1304.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 174, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1304.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 24, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "1304.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1305.cpp", "nloc": 71, "token_count": 909, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44034069", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 67, "token_count": 898, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1305.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1306.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44025045", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 75, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll need)", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["need"], "filename": "1306.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "1306.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1307.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 263, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44023824", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 54, "name": "Jud", "long_name": "Jud( LL x)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1307.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1307.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1308.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 283, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44015050", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 109, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( long long mid)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "1308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1309.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 418, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43920783", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "input", "long_name": "input()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1309.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 48, "name": "pw", "long_name": "pw( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1309.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 65, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1309.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 55, "name": "ans", "long_name": "ans( ll l , ll r)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1309.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1309.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "131.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43702135", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1310.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 418, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43912167", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "input", "long_name": "input()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1310.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 48, "name": "pw", "long_name": "pw( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1310.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 65, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1310.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 55, "name": "ans", "long_name": "ans( ll l , ll r)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1310.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1310.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1311.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 263, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43909867", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 245, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1311.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1312.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 322, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43901431", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 315, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1312.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1313.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 248, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43874687", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 213, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1313.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1314.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 484, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43808759", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "rand(m);", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 51, "token_count": 477, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 137, "parameters": [], "filename": "1314.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1315.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 371, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43806917", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 111, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( ll mid , ll r)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["mid", "r"], "filename": "1315.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "1315.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1316.cpp", "nloc": 231, "token_count": 1498, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43767419", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 20, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 13, "macro_count": 31, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 36, "name": "DisjointSet::DisjointSet", "long_name": "DisjointSet::DisjointSet( ll n)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 101, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 25, "name": "DisjointSet::root", "long_name": "DisjointSet::root( ll a)", "start_line": 102, "end_line": 104, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 77, "name": "DisjointSet::join", "long_name": "DisjointSet::join( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 118, "end_line": 120, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 98, "name": "isprime", "long_name": "isprime( ll n)", "start_line": 122, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 66, "name": "genPrime", "long_name": "genPrime( ll sz)", "start_line": 134, "end_line": 143, "parameters": ["sz"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 53, "name": "genFact", "long_name": "genFact( ll n)", "start_line": 148, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 58, "name": "genFactMod", "long_name": "genFactMod( ll n , ll mod)", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 164, "parameters": ["n", "mod"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 48, "name": "fact", "long_name": "fact( ll a , ll n)", "start_line": 166, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["a", "n"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 56, "name": "factMod", "long_name": "factMod( ll a , ll n , ll mod)", "start_line": 175, "end_line": 183, "parameters": ["a", "n", "mod"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 66, "name": "powMod", "long_name": "powMod( ll a , ll b , ll mod)", "start_line": 185, "end_line": 198, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "modularInverse", "long_name": "modularInverse( ll a , ll mod)", "start_line": 200, "end_line": 202, "parameters": ["a", "mod"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 44, "name": "ent", "long_name": "ent( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 204, "end_line": 209, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 58, "name": "entMod", "long_name": "entMod( ll a , ll b , ll mod)", "start_line": 211, "end_line": 216, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 47, "name": "bsfunction", "long_name": "bsfunction( ll n)", "start_line": 220, "end_line": 222, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 106, "name": "binarysearch", "long_name": "binarysearch( ll left , ll right , ll target)", "start_line": 224, "end_line": 237, "parameters": ["left", "right", "target"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 75, "name": "toposortvisit", "long_name": "toposortvisit( ll step)", "start_line": 245, "end_line": 258, "parameters": ["step"], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 80, "name": "toposort", "long_name": "toposort()", "start_line": 260, "end_line": 275, "parameters": [], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 108, "name": "MAIN", "long_name": "MAIN()", "start_line": 281, "end_line": 293, "parameters": [], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 40, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 303, "end_line": 323, "parameters": [], "filename": "1316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1317.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 326, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43766280", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 248, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1317.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1318.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43676555", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 48, "name": "cost", "long_name": "cost( long long n)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1318.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1318.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1319.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 416, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43642559", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 409, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1319.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "132.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43701764", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1320.cpp", "nloc": 75, "token_count": 390, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43598540", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 27, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln( Args ... args)", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 16, "parameters": ["args"], "filename": "1320.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 27, "name": "_db", "long_name": "_db( Args ... args)", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 24, "parameters": ["args"], "filename": "1320.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 8, "name": "_db", "long_name": "_db( Args ... args)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["args"], "filename": "1320.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 57, "token_count": 287, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1320.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1321.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 300, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43558814", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 100, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long tot)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["tot"], "filename": "1321.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1321.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1323.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 374, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43516289", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 27, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 287, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 229, "parameters": [], "filename": "1323.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1324.cpp", "nloc": 81, "token_count": 575, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43442675", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 32, "name": "mult", "long_name": "mult( ll a , ll b , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1324.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( ll a , ll b , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 14, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1324.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "sub", "long_name": "sub( ll a , ll b , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1324.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "fpow", "long_name": "fpow( ll n , ll k , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 16, "parameters": ["n", "k", "mod"], "filename": "1324.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( ll a , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["a", "mod"], "filename": "1324.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 71, "token_count": 376, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1324.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1325.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 437, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43423840", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 403, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 74, "parameters": [], "filename": "1325.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1326.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 364, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43416885", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 322, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1326.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1327.cpp", "nloc": 65, "token_count": 475, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43252431", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 63, "token_count": 468, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1327.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 125, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1328.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 367, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43174293", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 47, "name": "getPrice", "long_name": "getPrice( ll curr , ll N , ll n , ll p)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 9, "parameters": ["curr", "N", "n", "p"], "filename": "1328.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 308, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "1328.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1329.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43148215", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1329.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "133.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 252, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43698761", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 245, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "133.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1332.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 335, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43078213", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 72, "name": "juge", "long_name": "juge( ll x)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1332.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 56, "name": "binary_ans", "long_name": "binary_ans()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1332.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1332.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1333.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 327, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43025366", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 16, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 83, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( ll x)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "1333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1334.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 386, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43009311", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 378, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "1334.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1335.cpp", "nloc": 118, "token_count": 926, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43009217", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 45, "nloc": 115, "token_count": 918, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 301, "parameters": [], "filename": "1335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 275, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1336.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42899543", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 64, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1336.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1336.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1337.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42890955", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 209, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1337.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1338.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 471, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42870178", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 38, "name": "printprecise", "long_name": "printprecise( double l , ll precision)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["l", "precision"], "filename": "1338.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 32, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1338.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 357, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 167, "parameters": [], "filename": "1338.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1339.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 384, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42862320", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1339.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 65, "name": "powm", "long_name": "powm( ll base , ll exp , ll mod = MOD)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["base", "exp", "MOD"], "filename": "1339.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 75, "name": "price", "long_name": "price( ll n)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1339.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1339.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "134.cpp", "nloc": 67, "token_count": 544, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43694209", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 61, "token_count": 516, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 207, "parameters": [], "filename": "134.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 151, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1340.cpp", "nloc": 59, "token_count": 316, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42749590", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 21, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 213, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1340.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1341.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42542649", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 77, "name": "judge", "long_name": "judge( ll x)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1342.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42542623", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 77, "name": "judge", "long_name": "judge( ll x)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1342.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1342.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1343.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 443, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42498163", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "sc", "long_name": "sc( int & _x)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["_x"], "filename": "1343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "sc", "long_name": "sc( int & _x , int & _y)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["_x", "_y"], "filename": "1343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 32, "name": "sc", "long_name": "sc( int & _x , int & _y , int & _z)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["_x", "_y", "_z"], "filename": "1343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 41, "name": "sc", "long_name": "sc( int & _x , int & _y , int & _z , int & _zz)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["_x", "_y", "_z", "_zz"], "filename": "1343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 86, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( ll m)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["m"], "filename": "1343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 75, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs()", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "1343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 167, "parameters": [], "filename": "1343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1344.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 302, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42496550", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "mag", "long_name": "mag( t a)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1344.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 70, "name": "pred", "long_name": "pred( ll k)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1344.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1344.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1345.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 431, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42478378", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "deb", "long_name": "deb( T1 e1)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["e1"], "filename": "1345.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 24, "name": "deb", "long_name": "deb( T1 e1 , T2 e2)", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["e1", "e2"], "filename": "1345.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 33, "name": "deb", "long_name": "deb( T1 e1 , T2 e2 , T3 e3)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["e1", "e2", "e3"], "filename": "1345.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 19, "name": "check_time", "long_name": "check_time()", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 151, "parameters": [], "filename": "1345.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 179, "end_line": 241, "parameters": [], "filename": "1345.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1346.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 230, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42349642", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1346.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1347.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 309, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42228008", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 78, "name": "can", "long_name": "can( ll a)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1347.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 205, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1347.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1348.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 378, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42189987", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 132, "name": "sePuede", "long_name": "sePuede( ll sanguches , ll a , ll b , ll c , ll a1 , ll b1 , ll c1 , ll a2 , ll b2 , ll c2)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["sanguches", "a", "b", "c", "a1", "b1", "c1", "a2", "b2", "c2"], "filename": "1348.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 230, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1348.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1349.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 220, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42154516", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 211, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 19, "parameters": [], "filename": "1349.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "135.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43693080", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1350.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 296, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41995523", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 75, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long mid)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "1350.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "1350.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1351.cpp", "nloc": 63, "token_count": 346, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41985085", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 106, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( lld k)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1351.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 75, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 149, "parameters": [], "filename": "1351.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 100, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 187, "parameters": [], "filename": "1351.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 30, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 189, "end_line": 201, "parameters": [], "filename": "1351.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1352.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 456, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41975012", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 26, "nloc": 54, "token_count": 436, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "1352.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1353.cpp", "nloc": 109, "token_count": 968, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41970059", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 9, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 24, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( istream_iterator<string> it)", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 28, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "1353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 41, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( istream_iterator<string> it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 34, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "1353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 46, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: pair<T1,T2> & p)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 40, "parameters": ["os", "p"], "filename": "1353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 81, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 90, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: set<T> & v)", "start_line": 58, "end_line": 70, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 94, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: map<T1,T2> & v)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 46, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: unordered_set<T> & v)", "start_line": 88, "end_line": 90, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 50, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: unordered_map<T1,T2> & v)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "1353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 401, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "1353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1354.cpp", "nloc": 93, "token_count": 472, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41889072", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 41, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( int a , int b , int c)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "1354.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 79, "token_count": 417, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 195, "parameters": [], "filename": "1354.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 157, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1355.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 375, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41760343", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 23, "nloc": 55, "token_count": 361, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "1355.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 115, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1356.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 301, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41675462", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 66, "name": "cek", "long_name": "cek( LL x)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1357.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41605569", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 26, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ll a , ll b , ll c)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["a", "b", "c"], "filename": "1357.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1357.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1358.cpp", "nloc": 94, "token_count": 1116, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41601503", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 14, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod( int n)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1358.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 35, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1358.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 5, "name": "ingr::ingr", "long_name": "ingr::ingr()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1358.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "ingr::ingr", "long_name": "ingr::ingr( int n , int q , int p)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["n", "q", "p"], "filename": "1358.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 31, "name": "cmp", "long_name": "cmp( const ingr & a , const ingr & b)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1358.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 78, "token_count": 970, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 239, "parameters": [], "filename": "1358.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 167, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1359.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 436, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41581035", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 322, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "1359.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "136.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43692673", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "136.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1360.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 302, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41459508", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 74, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long value)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["value"], "filename": "1360.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 135, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "1360.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1362.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 485, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41280129", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 469, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1362.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1364.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 322, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41223714", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 92, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( ll x)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1364.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 167, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1364.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1365.cpp", "nloc": 69, "token_count": 732, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41177900", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 11, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "getbit", "long_name": "getbit( T s , int i)", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 46, "parameters": ["s", "i"], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "onbit", "long_name": "onbit( T s , int i)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["s", "i"], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 25, "name": "offbit", "long_name": "offbit( T s , int i)", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 48, "parameters": ["s", "i"], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "cntbit", "long_name": "cntbit( T s)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 41, "name": "Input", "long_name": "Input()", "start_line": 72, "end_line": 78, "parameters": [], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 163, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 80, "end_line": 106, "parameters": [], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 53, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 110, "end_line": 116, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 73, "name": "ControlIO", "long_name": "ControlIO( int argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 120, "end_line": 128, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "TimerStart", "long_name": "TimerStart()", "start_line": 130, "end_line": 134, "parameters": [], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 45, "name": "TimerStop", "long_name": "TimerStop()", "start_line": 136, "end_line": 142, "parameters": [], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 14, "name": "Exit", "long_name": "Exit()", "start_line": 144, "end_line": 146, "parameters": [], "filename": "1365.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1366.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 293, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41106006", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 262, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "1366.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1367.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 293, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/41010373", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 286, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "1367.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1368.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 441, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40989294", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 92, "name": "Work", "long_name": "Work( long long k)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 28, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1368.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 62, "name": "BinarySearch", "long_name": "BinarySearch( long long l , long long r)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 36, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1368.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1368.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1369.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 335, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40864389", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 120, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long bb)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["bb"], "filename": "1369.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 187, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1369.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "137.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 148, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43690308", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "137.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1370.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 422, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40844311", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "my_mod", "long_name": "my_mod( ll num , ll mod)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["num", "mod"], "filename": "1370.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1370.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 79, "name": "can", "long_name": "can( ll num)", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["num"], "filename": "1370.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "1370.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1371.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 498, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40759870", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 479, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 50, "parameters": [], "filename": "1371.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1372.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 289, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40723241", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 220, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "1372.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1373.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 370, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40692119", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 34, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 84, "name": "can", "long_name": "can( ll k)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1373.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 195, "parameters": [], "filename": "1373.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1374.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 361, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40686615", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 94, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long x)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1374.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 233, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1374.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1375.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 266, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40686425", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 59, "name": "isValid", "long_name": "isValid( ll x)", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 14, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1375.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1375.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 30, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1376.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 306, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40675722", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 57, "name": "afford", "long_name": "afford( LL num)", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 16, "parameters": ["num"], "filename": "1376.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "1376.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1377.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 566, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40669863", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 86, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1377.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 103, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read( mitsuha & x)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1377.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 91, "name": "chtholly::write", "long_name": "chtholly::write( mitsuha x)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1377.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "chtholly::fuhao", "long_name": "chtholly::fuhao()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1377.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 70, "name": "judge", "long_name": "judge( ll x)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 101, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1377.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "1377.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1378.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 304, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40608518", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 47, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll x)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1378.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 203, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1378.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1379.cpp", "nloc": 61, "token_count": 384, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40594296", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 44, "name": "fenjie", "long_name": "fenjie( int len)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["len"], "filename": "1379.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 92, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll mid)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "1379.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 104, "name": "erfen", "long_name": "erfen()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1379.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 137, "parameters": [], "filename": "1379.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "138.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 271, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43687741", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 260, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1380.cpp", "nloc": 86, "token_count": 677, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40577903", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 65, "name": "dfs", "long_name": "dfs( int start)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["start"], "filename": "1380.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 73, "token_count": 570, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 181, "parameters": [], "filename": "1380.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 153, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1381.cpp", "nloc": 67, "token_count": 839, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40521872", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 10, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "issquare", "long_name": "issquare( ll w)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["w"], "filename": "1381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 43, "name": "isprime", "long_name": "isprime( ll u)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["u"], "filename": "1381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 32, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod( ll to_mod , ll modulo = MOD)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["to_mod", "MOD"], "filename": "1381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 63, "name": "moduloMultiplication", "long_name": "moduloMultiplication( ll a , ll b , ll mod)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 59, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "1381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 36, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( ll v1 , ll v2)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["v1", "v2"], "filename": "1381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 86, "name": "possible", "long_name": "possible( ll u)", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 137, "parameters": ["u"], "filename": "1381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 201, "parameters": [], "filename": "1381.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1382.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 347, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40498744", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 84, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll x)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1382.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 73, "name": "bb", "long_name": "bb( ll l , ll r , ll val)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["l", "r", "val"], "filename": "1382.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1382.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1383.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40355999", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 234, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1383.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1384.cpp", "nloc": 70, "token_count": 448, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/40073567", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 18, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 83, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "1384.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 82, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1384.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 145, "name": "I_Love_Hashimoto_Kanna", "long_name": "I_Love_Hashimoto_Kanna()", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 191, "parameters": [], "filename": "1384.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1385.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 244, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/39430884", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 69, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int k)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1385.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 53, "name": "binsearch", "long_name": "binsearch( int lo , int hi)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["lo", "hi"], "filename": "1385.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 89, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1385.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1386.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 312, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/39059170", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 301, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "1386.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1387.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 457, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/39044823", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 381, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 183, "parameters": [], "filename": "1387.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 125, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1388.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 241, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/37559541", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "3400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 75, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( ll x)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1388.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1388.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1389.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 265, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/36614995", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "3300 KB", "usertype": "KajuBadaamBiscuit", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 70, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll x)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1389.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1389.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "139.cpp", "nloc": 13, "token_count": 60, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/44078969", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 53, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "139.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1390.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 280, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/36271072", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 62, "name": "process", "long_name": "process( long long t)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["t"], "filename": "1390.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1390.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1391.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 309, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/36145058", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 88, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( long long x)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1391.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "1391.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1392.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 307, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/35451545", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 267, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "1392.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 30, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1392.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1393.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 302, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/35182085", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 75, "name": "cost", "long_name": "cost( long long x)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1393.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 200, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1393.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1394.cpp", "nloc": 109, "token_count": 501, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/35158611", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 105, "token_count": 457, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 225, "parameters": [], "filename": "1394.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 217, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1395.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 334, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/34980366", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 109, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long mid)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "1395.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "1395.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1396.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 410, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/34641470", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 28, "name": "getInd", "long_name": "getInd( char ch)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["ch"], "filename": "1396.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 30, "name": "isEnd", "long_name": "isEnd()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1396.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 261, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 179, "parameters": [], "filename": "1396.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1397.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 297, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/34582778", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Earth_is_Flat", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 285, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "1397.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1398.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 286, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/33592766", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 16, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 65, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll n)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1398.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 173, "parameters": [], "filename": "1398.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1399.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/33508853", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 128, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int v)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "1399.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "1399.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "14.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44044838", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "14.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "140.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 487, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/44074946", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "8500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 86, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read()", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 19, "parameters": [], "filename": "140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 103, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read( mitsuha & x)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 91, "name": "chtholly::write", "long_name": "chtholly::write( mitsuha x)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 36, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "chtholly::fuhao", "long_name": "chtholly::fuhao()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 78, "name": "get", "long_name": "get( ll n , ll l , ll r , ll k)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 50, "parameters": ["n", "l", "r", "k"], "filename": "140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 41, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1400.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/33233113", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 66, "name": "input", "long_name": "input()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "1400.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 87, "name": "doable", "long_name": "doable( long long target)", "start_line": 36, "end_line": 58, "parameters": ["target"], "filename": "1400.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 85, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 82, "parameters": [], "filename": "1400.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 19, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1400.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1401.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 320, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/33055264", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 101, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( LL n)", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 19, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1401.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "1401.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1402.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 328, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/32493779", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 81, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1402.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 202, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "1402.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1403.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 298, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/32178626", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 291, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "1403.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1404.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44099663", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 25, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 113, "name": "possible", "long_name": "possible( ll x)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 52, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 78, "parameters": [], "filename": "1404.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1405.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 364, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44082694", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 327, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "1405.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1406.cpp", "nloc": 156, "token_count": 749, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44075890", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 185, "name": "ha", "long_name": "ha()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1406.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 153, "name": "ch", "long_name": "ch( ll wgh)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 143, "parameters": ["wgh"], "filename": "1406.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 94, "token_count": 361, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 331, "parameters": [], "filename": "1406.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 187, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1407.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 351, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44036949", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 262, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 149, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1407.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1408.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 313, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44034887", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 32, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 81, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1408.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 174, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1408.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 24, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "1408.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1409.cpp", "nloc": 71, "token_count": 909, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44034069", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 67, "token_count": 898, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1409.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "141.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 487, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/44073188", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "8200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 86, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 103, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read( mitsuha & x)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 91, "name": "chtholly::write", "long_name": "chtholly::write( mitsuha x)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "chtholly::fuhao", "long_name": "chtholly::fuhao()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 78, "name": "get", "long_name": "get( ll n , ll l , ll r , ll k)", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["n", "l", "r", "k"], "filename": "141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 41, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1410.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44025045", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 75, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll need)", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["need"], "filename": "1410.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "1410.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1411.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 263, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44023824", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 54, "name": "Jud", "long_name": "Jud( LL x)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1411.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "1411.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1412.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 283, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/44015050", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 109, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( long long mid)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "1412.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "1412.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1413.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 418, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43920783", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "input", "long_name": "input()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1413.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 48, "name": "pw", "long_name": "pw( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1413.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 65, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1413.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 55, "name": "ans", "long_name": "ans( ll l , ll r)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1413.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1413.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1414.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 418, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43912167", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "input", "long_name": "input()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "1414.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 48, "name": "pw", "long_name": "pw( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1414.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 65, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1414.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 55, "name": "ans", "long_name": "ans( ll l , ll r)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "1414.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1414.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1415.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 263, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43909867", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 245, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "1415.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1416.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 322, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43901431", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 315, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "1416.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1417.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 248, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43874687", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 213, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "1417.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1418.cpp", "nloc": 53, "token_count": 484, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43808759", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "rand(m);", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 51, "token_count": 477, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 137, "parameters": [], "filename": "1418.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1419.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 371, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43806917", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 111, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( ll mid , ll r)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["mid", "r"], "filename": "1419.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "1419.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "142.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 118, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/44068885", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 43, "name": "qpow", "long_name": "qpow( ll p , ll k)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["p", "k"], "filename": "142.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 57, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "142.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1420.cpp", "nloc": 231, "token_count": 1498, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43767419", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 20, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 13, "macro_count": 31, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 36, "name": "DisjointSet::DisjointSet", "long_name": "DisjointSet::DisjointSet( ll n)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 101, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 25, "name": "DisjointSet::root", "long_name": "DisjointSet::root( ll a)", "start_line": 102, "end_line": 104, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 77, "name": "DisjointSet::join", "long_name": "DisjointSet::join( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 118, "end_line": 120, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 98, "name": "isprime", "long_name": "isprime( ll n)", "start_line": 122, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 66, "name": "genPrime", "long_name": "genPrime( ll sz)", "start_line": 134, "end_line": 143, "parameters": ["sz"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 53, "name": "genFact", "long_name": "genFact( ll n)", "start_line": 148, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 58, "name": "genFactMod", "long_name": "genFactMod( ll n , ll mod)", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 164, "parameters": ["n", "mod"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 48, "name": "fact", "long_name": "fact( ll a , ll n)", "start_line": 166, "end_line": 173, "parameters": ["a", "n"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 56, "name": "factMod", "long_name": "factMod( ll a , ll n , ll mod)", "start_line": 175, "end_line": 183, "parameters": ["a", "n", "mod"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 66, "name": "powMod", "long_name": "powMod( ll a , ll b , ll mod)", "start_line": 185, "end_line": 198, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "modularInverse", "long_name": "modularInverse( ll a , ll mod)", "start_line": 200, "end_line": 202, "parameters": ["a", "mod"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 44, "name": "ent", "long_name": "ent( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 204, "end_line": 209, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 58, "name": "entMod", "long_name": "entMod( ll a , ll b , ll mod)", "start_line": 211, "end_line": 216, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 47, "name": "bsfunction", "long_name": "bsfunction( ll n)", "start_line": 220, "end_line": 222, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 106, "name": "binarysearch", "long_name": "binarysearch( ll left , ll right , ll target)", "start_line": 224, "end_line": 237, "parameters": ["left", "right", "target"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 75, "name": "toposortvisit", "long_name": "toposortvisit( ll step)", "start_line": 245, "end_line": 258, "parameters": ["step"], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 80, "name": "toposort", "long_name": "toposort()", "start_line": 260, "end_line": 275, "parameters": [], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 108, "name": "MAIN", "long_name": "MAIN()", "start_line": 281, "end_line": 293, "parameters": [], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 40, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 303, "end_line": 323, "parameters": [], "filename": "1420.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1421.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 326, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43766280", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 248, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "1421.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1422.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43676555", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 48, "name": "cost", "long_name": "cost( long long n)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1422.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "1422.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1423.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 416, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43642559", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 409, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "1423.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1424.cpp", "nloc": 75, "token_count": 390, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43598540", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 27, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln( Args ... args)", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 16, "parameters": ["args"], "filename": "1424.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 27, "name": "_db", "long_name": "_db( Args ... args)", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 24, "parameters": ["args"], "filename": "1424.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 8, "name": "_db", "long_name": "_db( Args ... args)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["args"], "filename": "1424.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 57, "token_count": 287, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1424.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1425.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 300, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43558814", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 100, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( long long tot)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["tot"], "filename": "1425.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1425.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1427.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 374, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43516289", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 27, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 287, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 229, "parameters": [], "filename": "1427.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1428.cpp", "nloc": 81, "token_count": 575, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43442675", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 32, "name": "mult", "long_name": "mult( ll a , ll b , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1428.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( ll a , ll b , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 14, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1428.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "sub", "long_name": "sub( ll a , ll b , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "1428.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "fpow", "long_name": "fpow( ll n , ll k , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 16, "parameters": ["n", "k", "mod"], "filename": "1428.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( ll a , ll p = mod)", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["a", "mod"], "filename": "1428.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 71, "token_count": 376, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1428.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1429.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 437, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43423840", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 20, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 403, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 74, "parameters": [], "filename": "1429.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "143.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 118, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/44068876", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 43, "name": "qpow", "long_name": "qpow( ll p , ll k)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 18, "parameters": ["p", "k"], "filename": "143.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 57, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "143.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1430.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 364, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43416885", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 322, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1430.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1431.cpp", "nloc": 65, "token_count": 475, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43252431", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 63, "token_count": 468, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "1431.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 125, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1432.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 367, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43174293", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 47, "name": "getPrice", "long_name": "getPrice( ll curr , ll N , ll n , ll p)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 9, "parameters": ["curr", "N", "n", "p"], "filename": "1432.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 308, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "1432.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1433.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43148215", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1433.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1436.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 335, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43078213", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 72, "name": "juge", "long_name": "juge( ll x)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1436.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 56, "name": "binary_ans", "long_name": "binary_ans()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "1436.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "1436.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1437.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 327, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43025366", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 16, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 83, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok( ll x)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1437.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "1437.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1438.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 386, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43009311", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 378, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "1438.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1439.cpp", "nloc": 118, "token_count": 926, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/43009217", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 45, "nloc": 115, "token_count": 918, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 301, "parameters": [], "filename": "1439.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 275, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "144.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 487, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/44068696", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "8200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 86, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read()", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 19, "parameters": [], "filename": "144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 103, "name": "chtholly::read", "long_name": "chtholly::read( mitsuha & x)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 91, "name": "chtholly::write", "long_name": "chtholly::write( mitsuha x)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 36, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 30, "name": "chtholly::fuhao", "long_name": "chtholly::fuhao()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 78, "name": "get", "long_name": "get( ll n , ll l , ll r , ll k)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 50, "parameters": ["n", "l", "r", "k"], "filename": "144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 41, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 56, "parameters": [], "filename": "144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1440.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42899543", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 64, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1440.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "1440.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1441.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42890955", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 209, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "1441.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1442.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 471, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42870178", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 38, "name": "printprecise", "long_name": "printprecise( double l , ll precision)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["l", "precision"], "filename": "1442.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 32, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1442.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 357, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 167, "parameters": [], "filename": "1442.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1443.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 384, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42862320", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "1443.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 65, "name": "powm", "long_name": "powm( ll base , ll exp , ll mod = MOD)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["base", "exp", "MOD"], "filename": "1443.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 75, "name": "price", "long_name": "price( ll n)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "1443.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "1443.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1444.cpp", "nloc": 59, "token_count": 316, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42749590", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 21, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 213, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1444.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1445.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42542649", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 77, "name": "judge", "long_name": "judge( ll x)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1445.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1445.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1446.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42542623", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 77, "name": "judge", "long_name": "judge( ll x)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "1446.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "1446.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1447.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 443, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42498163", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "sc", "long_name": "sc( int & _x)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["_x"], "filename": "1447.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "sc", "long_name": "sc( int & _x , int & _y)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["_x", "_y"], "filename": "1447.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 32, "name": "sc", "long_name": "sc( int & _x , int & _y , int & _z)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["_x", "_y", "_z"], "filename": "1447.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 41, "name": "sc", "long_name": "sc( int & _x , int & _y , int & _z , int & _zz)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["_x", "_y", "_z", "_zz"], "filename": "1447.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 86, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( ll m)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["m"], "filename": "1447.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 75, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs()", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "1447.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 167, "parameters": [], "filename": "1447.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1448.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 302, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42496550", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "mag", "long_name": "mag( t a)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "1448.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 70, "name": "pred", "long_name": "pred( ll k)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "1448.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "1448.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1449.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 431, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42478378", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "deb", "long_name": "deb( T1 e1)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["e1"], "filename": "1449.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 24, "name": "deb", "long_name": "deb( T1 e1 , T2 e2)", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["e1", "e2"], "filename": "1449.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 33, "name": "deb", "long_name": "deb( T1 e1 , T2 e2 , T3 e3)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["e1", "e2", "e3"], "filename": "1449.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 19, "name": "check_time", "long_name": "check_time()", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 151, "parameters": [], "filename": "1449.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 179, "end_line": 241, "parameters": [], "filename": "1449.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "145.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/44043693", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 76, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll lo , ll hi , ll k , int n)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["lo", "hi", "k", "n"], "filename": "145.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "145.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "1450.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 230, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/371/submission/42349642", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "1450.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "146.cpp", "nloc": 10, "token_count": 38, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/44039838", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 18, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 29, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "146.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "147.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 115, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/44036408", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "147.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "148.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43983257", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 74, "name": "search", "long_name": "search( ll low , ll high , ll n , ll k)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["low", "high", "n", "k"], "filename": "148.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 65, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "148.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "149.cpp", "nloc": 124, "token_count": 756, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43941794", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 10, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 65, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "BINARY_SEARCH", "long_name": "BINARY_SEARCH( ll dp [ ] , ll n , ll key)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["]", "n", "key"], "filename": "149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 55, "name": "CONVERT_TO_BINARY", "long_name": "CONVERT_TO_BINARY( ll s)", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 55, "name": "PALIN", "long_name": "PALIN( string s)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 53, "name": "STOI", "long_name": "STOI( string s)", "start_line": 155, "end_line": 171, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 20, "name": "modInverse", "long_name": "modInverse( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 173, "end_line": 177, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 157, "name": "findLongestSub", "long_name": "findLongestSub( string bin)", "start_line": 185, "end_line": 283, "parameters": ["bin"], "filename": "149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 98, "name": "prefix_KMP", "long_name": "prefix_KMP( string & s)", "start_line": 285, "end_line": 315, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 16, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( ll l , ll r , ll need , ll Size)", "start_line": 317, "end_line": 323, "parameters": ["l", "r", "need", "Size"], "filename": "149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 325, "end_line": 381, "parameters": [], "filename": "149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "15.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 198, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44043904", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "15.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "150.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 93, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43917399", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "151.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 67, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43823127", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 60, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "151.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "152.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 105, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43806537", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 62, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "152.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "153.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 595, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43753289", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 10, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "fpow", "long_name": "fpow( ll n , ll k , ll p = MOD)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["n", "k", "MOD"], "filename": "153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( ll a , ll p = MOD)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "MOD"], "filename": "153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 91, "name": "Sqrt", "long_name": "Sqrt( ll x)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 69, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 36, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 83, "name": "in", "long_name": "in( ll & no)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["no"], "filename": "153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "maxx", "long_name": "maxx( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 82, "name": "find", "long_name": "find( ll l , ll r , ll k , ll n)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["l", "r", "k", "n"], "filename": "153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 66, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "154.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 130, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43728884", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "154.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "155.cpp", "nloc": 9, "token_count": 51, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43720127", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 39, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "155.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "156.cpp", "nloc": 10, "token_count": 85, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43699017", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 78, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "156.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "157.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 110, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43671308", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 76, "name": "foo", "long_name": "foo( long long n , long long x)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["n", "x"], "filename": "157.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 26, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "157.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "158.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 122, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43669828", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 82, "name": "fun", "long_name": "fun( lli k)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "158.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 32, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "158.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "159.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43662653", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 69, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "159.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 77, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( ll n , ll k)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "159.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 34, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "159.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "16.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 210, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44041144", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "16.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "160.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 82, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43650069", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 67, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "161.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 161, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43646888", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 70, "name": "pow_", "long_name": "pow_( ll x , unsigned ll y)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "161.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "161.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "162.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 109, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43646130", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "162.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "163.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 99, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43645639", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 80, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "163.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "164.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43641773", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 63, "name": "FP", "long_name": "FP( ll n , ll x)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["n", "x"], "filename": "164.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 73, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "164.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "165.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 90, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43618552", "exec_time": "15 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "165.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "166.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 375, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43616499", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 11, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "two", "long_name": "two( int n)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "test", "long_name": "test( int n , int b)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "set_bit", "long_name": "set_bit( int & n , int b)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "unset_bit", "long_name": "unset_bit( int & n , int b)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "last_bit", "long_name": "last_bit( int n)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "ones", "long_name": "ones( int n)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "EQ", "long_name": "EQ( double a , double b)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "chmax", "long_name": "chmax( T & a , const T & b)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "chmin", "long_name": "chmin( T & a , const T & b)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 71, "name": "fn", "long_name": "fn( int i , ll_ j)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 51, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "167.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43614120", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "167.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "168.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 96, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43536451", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 89, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "169.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 85, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43536404", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 78, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "17.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44038547", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 181, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "17.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "170.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 267, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43518219", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 23, "name": "io", "long_name": "io()", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 65, "name": "fast_exp", "long_name": "fast_exp( ll base , int exp , int m)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["base", "exp", "m"], "filename": "170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 83, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( ll n , ll k)", "start_line": 62, "end_line": 74, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 31, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 76, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "171.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 123, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/743/submission/43517479", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "171.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "171.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "172.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 168, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/44093806", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "173.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/44092291", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "173.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "174.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 286, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/44074140", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 149, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "174.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "175.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/44068529", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 36, "parameters": [], "filename": "175.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "176.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/44049191", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 36, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "176.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "177.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/44047328", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "177.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "178.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 217, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/44039765", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "178.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "179.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/44027566", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 49, "name": "can", "long_name": "can( ll x)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "179.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 109, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "179.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "18.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 335, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44036287", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 326, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "18.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "180.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43986420", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "180.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "181.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43979447", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "181.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 32, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "182.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43978986", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 184, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "182.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "183.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 121, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43969611", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 109, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "184.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 105, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43969311", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "184.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "185.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 273, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43960246", "exec_time": "434 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "185.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "186.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 250, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43952271", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 243, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "186.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "187.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 282, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43937646", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "3400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 238, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 143, "parameters": [], "filename": "187.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "188.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 217, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43929099", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 32, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 173, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "188.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 24, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "188.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "189.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43928938", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 211, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "189.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "19.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 308, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44032820", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 18, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 39, "token_count": 299, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "19.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "190.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43921423", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "190.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "191.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43919705", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 184, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "191.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "192.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43917641", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "193.cpp", "nloc": 65, "token_count": 382, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43910341", "exec_time": "278 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 23, "used_headers": 5, "macro_count": 23, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "amin", "long_name": "amin( T & x , U y)", "start_line": 147, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "amax", "long_name": "amax( T & x , U y)", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 149, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 19, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( int a , int b)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 201, "parameters": [], "filename": "193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "194.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43880235", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "194.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "195.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43880008", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 166, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "195.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "196.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43870868", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "196.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "197.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43824855", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "197.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "198.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 129, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43813602", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "198.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "199.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43809541", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "199.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "2.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44079851", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "2.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "20.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44031970", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 216, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "20.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "200.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 379, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43802216", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 49, "name": "sortpair", "long_name": "sortpair( const pair<int,int> & x , const pair<int,int> & y)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 31, "name": "dcomp", "long_name": "dcomp( double x , double y)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "smile", "long_name": "smile()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 36, "name": "printarr", "long_name": "printarr( ll arr [ ] , int n)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["]", "n"], "filename": "200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 67, "name": "BS_prefix", "long_name": "BS_prefix( int l , int r , int t , int indx)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 125, "parameters": ["l", "r", "t", "indx"], "filename": "200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 98, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 157, "parameters": [], "filename": "200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "201.cpp", "nloc": 48, "token_count": 407, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43800884", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 49, "name": "sortpair", "long_name": "sortpair( const pair<int,int> & x , const pair<int,int> & y)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "201.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 31, "name": "dcomp", "long_name": "dcomp( double x , double y)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "201.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "smile", "long_name": "smile()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "201.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 36, "name": "printarr", "long_name": "printarr( ll arr [ ] , int n)", "start_line": 95, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["]", "n"], "filename": "201.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 84, "name": "BS_prefix", "long_name": "BS_prefix( int n , ll v)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["n", "v"], "filename": "201.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 109, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 153, "parameters": [], "filename": "201.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "202.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 156, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43796809", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "203.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43793666", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 46, "name": "nhap", "long_name": "nhap()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 45, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int x)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 62, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 54, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "204.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 225, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43754732", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "204.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "205.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43749342", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 91, "name": "valid", "long_name": "valid( int x)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "205.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "205.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "206.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43740183", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "206.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "207.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43725985", "exec_time": "372 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "208.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43725940", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "209.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 396, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43717131", "exec_time": "186 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "_f", "long_name": "_f( const char * name , T && arg)", "start_line": 20, "end_line": 22, "parameters": ["name", "arg"], "filename": "209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 60, "name": "_f", "long_name": "_f( const char * names , T && arg , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["names", "arg", "args"], "filename": "209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 227, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char ** argv)", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["argc", "argv"], "filename": "209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 38, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "21.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44031362", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "21.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "210.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43706501", "exec_time": "154 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "211.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 343, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43704815", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 12, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "211.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 55, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll n)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["x", "n"], "filename": "211.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "211.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "212.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 402, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43697350", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 28, "name": "fast", "long_name": "fast()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 17, "parameters": [], "filename": "212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 72, "name": "lucky", "long_name": "lucky( long long a , long long c , int b)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["a", "c", "b"], "filename": "212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 68, "name": "fff", "long_name": "fff( string s , int c)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["s", "c"], "filename": "212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 66, "name": "toint", "long_name": "toint( string s)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "213.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 581, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43689708", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 9, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 57, "name": "fpow", "long_name": "fpow( ll n , ll k , ll p = MOD)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["n", "k", "MOD"], "filename": "213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( ll a , ll p = MOD)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "MOD"], "filename": "213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 91, "name": "Sqrt", "long_name": "Sqrt( ll x)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 69, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 36, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 83, "name": "in", "long_name": "in( ll & no)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["no"], "filename": "213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "maxx", "long_name": "maxx( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 135, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "214.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43689076", "exec_time": "186 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "215.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43673595", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "8100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 67, "name": "can", "long_name": "can( int m)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["m"], "filename": "215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "216.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43672450", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "217.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43666380", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "217.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "218.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43624995", "exec_time": "278 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "218.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "219.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43624458", "exec_time": "122 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "219.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "22.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44030767", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "17100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 224, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "22.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 105, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "220.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 130, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43622243", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "220.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "221.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43620292", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "222.cpp", "nloc": 119, "token_count": 755, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43616317", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 127, "name": "scan", "long_name": "scan( T & x)", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 94, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( T n)", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 72, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 121, "name": "readint", "long_name": "readint()", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 131, "name": "readll", "long_name": "readll()", "start_line": 94, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 106, "name": "sliding_window_chutiyaap", "long_name": "sliding_window_chutiyaap( int a [ ] , int n , int k)", "start_line": 116, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["]", "n", "k"], "filename": "222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 79, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 136, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "223.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 131, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43615401", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 124, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "224.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 125, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43615354", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 118, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "225.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 417, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43614125", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 10, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "two", "long_name": "two( int n)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "test", "long_name": "test( int n , int b)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "set_bit", "long_name": "set_bit( int & n , int b)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "unset_bit", "long_name": "unset_bit( int & n , int b)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["n", "b"], "filename": "225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "last_bit", "long_name": "last_bit( int n)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "ones", "long_name": "ones( int n)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "EQ", "long_name": "EQ( double a , double b)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "chmax", "long_name": "chmax( T & a , const T & b)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "chmin", "long_name": "chmin( T & a , const T & b)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 133, "parameters": [], "filename": "225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "226.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43610847", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "226.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "227.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 107, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43596974", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "227.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "228.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43594432", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "228.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "229.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43593297", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "229.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "23.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44028796", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 121, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "23.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "230.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43585362", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 152, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 34, "parameters": [], "filename": "230.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 32, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "231.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43577807", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "231.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "232.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43573332", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "233.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43568332", "exec_time": "278 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "233.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "234.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 277, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43561233", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 25, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( long long a , long long b)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "234.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 25, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( long long a , long long b)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "234.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 29, "name": "swap", "long_name": "swap( int * pa , int * pb)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["pa", "pb"], "filename": "234.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 30, "name": "get", "long_name": "get( int a)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "234.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 175, "parameters": [], "filename": "234.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "235.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 129, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43558730", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "236.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 129, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43558701", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "237.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 132, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43557728", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "237.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "238.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43556752", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "238.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "239.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43540843", "exec_time": "372 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "239.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "24.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44025405", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "24.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "240.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43540790", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "240.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "241.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43540664", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "241.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "242.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43540575", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 137, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "242.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "243.cpp", "nloc": 82, "token_count": 346, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43536982", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 30, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 199, "parameters": [], "filename": "243.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "244.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43534904", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "244.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "245.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 127, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43507036", "exec_time": "278 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "245.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "246.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43506876", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "246.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "247.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 271, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43505033", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 27, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 53, "token_count": 261, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 375, "end_line": 489, "parameters": [], "filename": "247.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 115, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "248.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 133, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43499097", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "248.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "249.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 160, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43497289", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "25.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44020892", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 116, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "25.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "250.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43496983", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "250.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "251.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 147, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43496017", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "251.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "252.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 325, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43490855", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 318, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 131, "parameters": [], "filename": "252.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 123, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "253.cpp", "nloc": 77, "token_count": 335, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43488455", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 69, "token_count": 308, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "253.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 147, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "254.cpp", "nloc": 84, "token_count": 454, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43483804", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 31, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int x , int y)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 31, "name": "lgcd", "long_name": "lgcd( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 64, "name": "pow", "long_name": "pow( ll a , ll b , ll m = MOD_7)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD_7"], "filename": "254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 83, "name": "gcdExtended", "long_name": "gcdExtended( ll a , ll b , ll * x , ll * y)", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 49, "name": "modInverse", "long_name": "modInverse( ll a , ll m = MOD_7)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 149, "parameters": ["a", "MOD_7"], "filename": "254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 157, "end_line": 213, "parameters": [], "filename": "254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "255.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43472855", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "256.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43470408", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "256.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "257.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 172, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43462362", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "257.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "258.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 108, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43454336", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 76, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "259.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 143, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43437130", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "259.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "26.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44017535", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "26.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "260.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 142, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43429913", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "260.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "261.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 131, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43428601", "exec_time": "278 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 105, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "261.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "262.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 203, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43427459", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "263.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43418913", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "263.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "264.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43413838", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "265.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43413021", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 221, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 40, "parameters": [], "filename": "265.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "266.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 173, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43389546", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 145, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "266.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "267.cpp", "nloc": 73, "token_count": 504, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43384961", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 123, "name": "binarySearch", "long_name": "binarySearch( int l , int r , int x)", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["l", "r", "x"], "filename": "267.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 64, "end_line": 88, "parameters": [], "filename": "267.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "268.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 108, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43383178", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "268.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "269.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 152, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43374970", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 139, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "269.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "27.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 249, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44013872", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 246, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "27.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "270.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43368689", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "272.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43361602", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 184, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "272.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "273.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43351440", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 131, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "273.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "274.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 133, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43346438", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 126, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "275.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 242, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43334975", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 59, "name": "cheak", "long_name": "cheak( int d)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["d"], "filename": "275.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "275.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "276.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43286974", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "277.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 163, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43268200", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "277.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "278.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43268079", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "278.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "279.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43265682", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "279.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "28.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 199, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44010524", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 36, "parameters": [], "filename": "28.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "280.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 218, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43265571", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "280.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "281.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43253230", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "281.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "282.cpp", "nloc": 66, "token_count": 316, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43252465", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1700 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 87, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( int n)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 93, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "282.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 65, "name": "calc", "long_name": "calc()", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "282.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 181, "parameters": [], "filename": "282.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "283.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43245587", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "283.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "284.cpp", "nloc": 102, "token_count": 540, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43240985", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "235600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 32, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 15, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "284.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 61, "name": "palindrome", "long_name": "palindrome( string s)", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "284.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 81, "name": "recursive", "long_name": "recursive( int n , int a [ ])", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 44, "parameters": ["n", "]"], "filename": "284.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 94, "name": "primeFactors", "long_name": "primeFactors( ll n , map<ll,ll> & m)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 70, "parameters": ["n", "m"], "filename": "284.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 238, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "284.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "285.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43240795", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "285.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "286.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 137, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43240261", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 118, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "286.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "287.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43239956", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "287.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "288.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43228836", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 32, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "289.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43183404", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "289.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "29.cpp", "nloc": 108, "token_count": 405, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44009168", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 76, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 79, "name": "valid", "long_name": "valid( double x)", "start_line": 132, "end_line": 141, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "29.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 113, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 144, "end_line": 169, "parameters": [], "filename": "29.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "290.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43180600", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "290.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "291.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43180427", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "291.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "292.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43155574", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "292.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "293.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43131853", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "293.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "294.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43128257", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "294.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "295.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 151, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43109592", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "295.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "296.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 137, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43109064", "exec_time": "278 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "296.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "297.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43106616", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "298.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 161, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43093065", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "298.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "299.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 114, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43090052", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "299.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44079713", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "30.cpp", "nloc": 63, "token_count": 399, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44007113", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 62, "name": "multiply", "long_name": "multiply( ll num1 , ll num2 , ll mod)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["num1", "num2", "mod"], "filename": "30.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 66, "name": "powmod2", "long_name": "powmod2( ll base , ll exponent , ll mod)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["base", "exponent", "mod"], "filename": "30.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 62, "name": "powmod", "long_name": "powmod( ll base , ll exponent , ll mod)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["base", "exponent", "mod"], "filename": "30.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 30, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 105, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "30.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 144, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "30.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "300.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43088707", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3000.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 140, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/44105301", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "8900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "3000.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3001.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 376, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/44075288", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "16900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 252, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "3001.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3002.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 202, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/44043910", "exec_time": "466 ms", "memory": "106300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "3002.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3003.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/44043890", "exec_time": "780 ms", "memory": "107200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "3003.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3004.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/44043871", "exec_time": "436 ms", "memory": "106300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 191, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "3004.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3005.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/44043784", "exec_time": "716 ms", "memory": "81200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "3005.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3006.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/44043769", "exec_time": "1216 ms", "memory": "88300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "3006.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3007.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/44042407", "exec_time": "684 ms", "memory": "174400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "3007.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3008.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 113, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/44010831", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "11700 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 99, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3008.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3009.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/44010380", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "9900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 32, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 129, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "3009.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 24, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "3009.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "301.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 150, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43085268", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "301.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3010.cpp", "nloc": 122, "token_count": 1054, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/44009642", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "11800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 12, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 23, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( istream_iterator<string> it)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["it"], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 41, "name": "err", "long_name": "err( istream_iterator<string> it , T a , Args ... args)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["it", "a", "args"], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "triple::triple", "long_name": "triple::triple()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "triple::triple", "long_name": "triple::triple( T1 _a , T2 _b , T3 _c)", "start_line": 44, "end_line": 44, "parameters": ["_a", "_b", "_c"], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 78, "name": "operator <", "long_name": "operator <( const triple<T1,T2,T3> & t1 , const triple<T1,T2,T3> & t2)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["t1", "t2"], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 46, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: pair<T1,T2> & p)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["os", "p"], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 81, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 66, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 90, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: set<T> & v)", "start_line": 68, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 94, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: map<T1,T2> & v)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 88, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 46, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: unordered_set<T> & v)", "start_line": 90, "end_line": 92, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 50, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( std :: ostream & os , const std :: unordered_map<T1,T2> & v)", "start_line": 94, "end_line": 96, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 285, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 153, "parameters": [], "filename": "3010.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3011.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 403, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43995410", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "13900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 52, "name": "is_prime", "long_name": "is_prime( ll n)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3011.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 49, "name": "getPow", "long_name": "getPow( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3011.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 50, "name": "coso", "long_name": "coso( ll x1 , ll y1 , ll x2 , ll y2 , ll x3 , ll y3)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2", "x3", "y3"], "filename": "3011.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 16, "name": "nxt", "long_name": "nxt()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "3011.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "ok", "long_name": "ok()", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "3011.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "no", "long_name": "no()", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "3011.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "3011.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3012.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 120, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43990449", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "10800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 78, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 36, "parameters": [], "filename": "3012.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3013.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 261, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43989228", "exec_time": "560 ms", "memory": "14800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 254, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "3013.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3014.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43982636", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "3014.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3015.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 126, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43938667", "exec_time": "590 ms", "memory": "80500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "3015.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3016.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43806332", "exec_time": "1216 ms", "memory": "64800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 209, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "3016.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3017.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 376, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43805300", "exec_time": "436 ms", "memory": "14800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 369, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "3017.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3018.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 454, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43712189", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "10800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 0, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "debugger::call", "long_name": "debugger::call( si it , si ed)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["it", "ed"], "filename": "3018.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 68, "name": "debugger::call", "long_name": "debugger::call( si it , si ed , T a , aT ... rest)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["it", "ed", "a", "rest"], "filename": "3018.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 17, "name": "in_generate", "long_name": "in_generate()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "3018.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 181, "parameters": [], "filename": "3018.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3019.cpp", "nloc": 76, "token_count": 473, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43661762", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "14800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 19, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 26, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 31, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll int a , ll int b)", "start_line": 54, "end_line": 58, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3019.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 64, "name": "fast_power", "long_name": "fast_power( ll int base , ll int power , ll int mod)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["base", "power", "mod"], "filename": "3019.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 107, "name": "scan", "long_name": "scan()", "start_line": 70, "end_line": 86, "parameters": [], "filename": "3019.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 216, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "3019.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "302.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43080245", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "302.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3020.cpp", "nloc": 87, "token_count": 530, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43660876", "exec_time": "404 ms", "memory": "23000 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 19, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 26, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 31, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll int a , ll int b)", "start_line": 54, "end_line": 58, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3020.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 64, "name": "fast_power", "long_name": "fast_power( ll int base , ll int power , ll int mod)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["base", "power", "mod"], "filename": "3020.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 107, "name": "scan", "long_name": "scan()", "start_line": 70, "end_line": 86, "parameters": [], "filename": "3020.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 273, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "3020.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3021.cpp", "nloc": 69, "token_count": 314, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43577558", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "9100 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 56, "token_count": 285, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "3021.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 127, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3022.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 223, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43574486", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "7700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 216, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "3022.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3023.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43500134", "exec_time": "748 ms", "memory": "6200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 258, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "3023.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3024.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 328, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43497725", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "9900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 264, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "3024.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 19, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "3024.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3025.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 314, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43399522", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "7500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 80, "name": "solve_0", "long_name": "solve_0()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "3025.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 187, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "3025.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3026.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 329, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43396050", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "7700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 308, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "3026.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3027.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 129, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43388819", "exec_time": "716 ms", "memory": "32600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 108, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 19, "parameters": [], "filename": "3027.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3028.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43168908", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "18000 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 18, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "3028.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3029.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 238, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43158193", "exec_time": "404 ms", "memory": "2900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "3029.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "303.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43075879", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "303.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3030.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43087512", "exec_time": "622 ms", "memory": "41800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "3030.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3031.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 327, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43075625", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "9900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "input", "long_name": "input()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "3031.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 48, "name": "pw", "long_name": "pw( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3031.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "3031.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3032.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43067537", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "9900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "3032.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3033.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43043684", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "16600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "3033.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3034.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 253, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43014441", "exec_time": "530 ms", "memory": "8600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 246, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "3034.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3035.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 233, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/43009642", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "8600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 226, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "3035.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3036.cpp", "nloc": 70, "token_count": 660, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/42908776", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "9900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 11, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 30, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "LCM", "long_name": "LCM( T a , T b)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 36, "name": "GCD", "long_name": "GCD( T a , T b)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "toString", "long_name": "toString( T a)", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "3036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "toInt", "long_name": "toInt( string s , T & x)", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 119, "parameters": ["s", "x"], "filename": "3036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "sub", "long_name": "sub( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 125, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 127, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 53, "name": "powr", "long_name": "powr( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( ll a)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 151, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "3036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 87, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll n)", "start_line": 163, "end_line": 179, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 191, "end_line": 241, "parameters": [], "filename": "3036.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3037.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 328, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/42893505", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "17700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 51, "token_count": 310, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "3037.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3038.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 159, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/42856020", "exec_time": "778 ms", "memory": "61800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "3038.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3039.cpp", "nloc": 68, "token_count": 858, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/42788140", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "16700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 12, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "smin", "long_name": "smin( T & a , const U & b)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "smax", "long_name": "smax( T & a , const U & b)", "start_line": 82, "end_line": 82, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 105, "name": "gn", "long_name": "gn( T & x)", "start_line": 88, "end_line": 88, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "gn", "long_name": "gn( T & x , T1 & y)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 91, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "gn", "long_name": "gn( T & x , T1 & y , T2 & z)", "start_line": 94, "end_line": 94, "parameters": ["x", "y", "z"], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 60, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( T x)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "println", "long_name": "println( T x)", "start_line": 100, "end_line": 100, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "printsp", "long_name": "printsp( T x)", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( T x , T1 y)", "start_line": 106, "end_line": 106, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "print", "long_name": "print( T x , T1 y , T2 z)", "start_line": 109, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["x", "y", "z"], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 59, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( int a , int b , int m , int ans = 1)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 124, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m", "1"], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 289, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 142, "end_line": 280, "parameters": [], "filename": "3039.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 139, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "304.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 108, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43073538", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "304.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3040.cpp", "nloc": 75, "token_count": 351, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/42763576", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 72, "token_count": 339, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "3040.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 149, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3041.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/42758201", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "18900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "3041.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3042.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 214, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/42751911", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 201, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "3042.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3043.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 364, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/42491546", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "26700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 69, "name": "ios::read", "long_name": "ios::read()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "3043.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 101, "name": "ios::operator > >", "long_name": "ios::operator > >( _Tp & x)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3043.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 106, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "3043.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3044.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/42449576", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "10100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "pwr", "long_name": "pwr( ll base , ll n , ll m)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["base", "n", "m"], "filename": "3044.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "3044.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3045.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/42244008", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "8600 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "3045.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3046.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/42012502", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "15000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 21, "name": "gausssum", "long_name": "gausssum( long long x)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 19, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3046.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 234, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "3046.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3047.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41926444", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3047.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3048.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41926160", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3048.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3049.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41837457", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "6800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "3049.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "305.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 168, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43072082", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "305.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3050.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 295, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41828519", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 286, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "3050.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3051.cpp", "nloc": 128, "token_count": 1097, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41650214", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "25600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 14, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 33, "name": "INPUT", "long_name": "INPUT( int * a , int size)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["a", "size"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 41, "name": "OUTPUT", "long_name": "OUTPUT( int * a , int size)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["a", "size"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( T1 a , T2 b)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( T1 a , T2 b)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 43, "name": "POW", "long_name": "POW( int a , int n)", "start_line": 139, "end_line": 159, "parameters": ["a", "n"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 26, "name": "to_string", "long_name": "to_string( int n)", "start_line": 165, "end_line": 179, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 42, "name": "to_binary", "long_name": "to_binary( int n)", "start_line": 185, "end_line": 203, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 76, "name": "GCD_E", "long_name": "GCD_E( int a , int b , int & x , int & y)", "start_line": 209, "end_line": 233, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 24, "name": "addMOD", "long_name": "addMOD( int a , int b , int m = MOD)", "start_line": 239, "end_line": 245, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 24, "name": "mulMOD", "long_name": "mulMOD( int a , int b , int m = MOD)", "start_line": 251, "end_line": 257, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 56, "name": "divMOD", "long_name": "divMOD( int a , int b , int m = MOD)", "start_line": 263, "end_line": 275, "parameters": ["a", "b", "MOD"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 34, "name": "C", "long_name": "C( int k , int n)", "start_line": 281, "end_line": 287, "parameters": ["k", "n"], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 202, "name": "solution", "long_name": "solution()", "start_line": 317, "end_line": 353, "parameters": [], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 39, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 357, "end_line": 379, "parameters": [], "filename": "3051.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3052.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 121, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41639580", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "3052.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3053.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 303, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41639313", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 276, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "3053.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3054.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 428, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41592102", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "35300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 392, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "3054.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3056.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 281, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41157966", "exec_time": "278 ms", "memory": "9400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 259, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "3056.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3057.cpp", "nloc": 73, "token_count": 613, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41154433", "exec_time": "590 ms", "memory": "10700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3057.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 79, "name": "pow", "long_name": "pow( T a , T b , ll m)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "b", "m"], "filename": "3057.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 52, "token_count": 339, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "3057.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 54, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3058.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 234, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41099451", "exec_time": "186 ms", "memory": "5400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 205, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "3058.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3059.cpp", "nloc": 54, "token_count": 407, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/41075758", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "6300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 110, "name": "bsearch1", "long_name": "bsearch1( int q , int ss , int ee)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["q", "ss", "ee"], "filename": "3059.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 112, "name": "bsearch2", "long_name": "bsearch2( int q , int ss , int ee)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["q", "ss", "ee"], "filename": "3059.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 163, "parameters": [], "filename": "3059.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "306.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43071830", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "306.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3060.cpp", "nloc": 75, "token_count": 490, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/40991671", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 42, "name": "Reader::read", "long_name": "Reader::read()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "3060.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "Reader::skip", "long_name": "Reader::skip()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "3060.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "Reader::Reader", "long_name": "Reader::Reader()", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "3060.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 37, "name": "Reader::nextInt", "long_name": "Reader::nextInt()", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "3060.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 256, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( char * s , int k)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 203, "parameters": ["s", "k"], "filename": "3060.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 48, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 207, "end_line": 239, "parameters": [], "filename": "3060.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3061.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 255, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/40918853", "exec_time": "622 ms", "memory": "6800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 248, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "3061.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3062.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 359, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/40868544", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "7700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "CERR_RED::operator < <", "long_name": "CERR_RED::operator < <( T && t)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 7, "parameters": ["t"], "filename": "3062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 32, "name": "CERR_RED::operator < <", "long_name": "CERR_RED::operator < <( std :: ostream &(*os)(std::ostream&))", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 9, "parameters": ["&"], "filename": "3062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 199, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "3062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 66, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "3062.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3063.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/40717927", "exec_time": "216 ms", "memory": "6000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 26, "parameters": [], "filename": "3063.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3064.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/40717878", "exec_time": "216 ms", "memory": "6000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "3064.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3065.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 253, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/40717762", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "9400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 222, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "3065.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3066.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 490, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/40712249", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "29100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 59, "token_count": 464, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "3066.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 117, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3067.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 181, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/40606802", "exec_time": "372 ms", "memory": "14800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "3067.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3069.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 565, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39988382", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "9900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3069.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3069.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "issquare", "long_name": "issquare( ll w)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["w"], "filename": "3069.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 43, "name": "isprime", "long_name": "isprime( ll u)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["u"], "filename": "3069.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod( ll to_mod)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["to_mod"], "filename": "3069.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 59, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3069.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 141, "parameters": [], "filename": "3069.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "307.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43071129", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "307.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3070.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39959178", "exec_time": "528 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "3070.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3071.cpp", "nloc": 73, "token_count": 472, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39873340", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "14800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 44, "name": "nod", "long_name": "nod( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3071.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 44, "name": "nod", "long_name": "nod( int a , int b)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3071.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "nok", "long_name": "nok( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 50, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3071.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "nok", "long_name": "nok( int a , int b)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3071.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "3071.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3072.cpp", "nloc": 66, "token_count": 474, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39868885", "exec_time": "904 ms", "memory": "41300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 13, "name": "in", "long_name": "in( T & a)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "3072.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 8, "name": "out", "long_name": "out( Args ... args)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["args"], "filename": "3072.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "out", "long_name": "out( Head head , Args ... args)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["head", "args"], "filename": "3072.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 17, "nloc": 51, "token_count": 385, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 177, "parameters": [], "filename": "3072.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 131, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3073.cpp", "nloc": 125, "token_count": 700, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39866179", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "9100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 10, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 51, "name": "DSU::DSU", "long_name": "DSU::DSU( int n)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 28, "name": "DSU::getRoot", "long_name": "DSU::getRoot( int ind)", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["ind"], "filename": "3073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 21, "name": "DSU::connected", "long_name": "DSU::connected( int ind1 , int ind2)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["ind1", "ind2"], "filename": "3073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 88, "name": "DSU::connect", "long_name": "DSU::connect( int ind1 , int ind2)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["ind1", "ind2"], "filename": "3073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 38, "name": "DSU::showId", "long_name": "DSU::showId( int n)", "start_line": 117, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 36, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 147, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcd", "long_name": "lcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 29, "name": "sgn", "long_name": "sgn( int n)", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 167, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 19, "name": "modS", "long_name": "modS( int a , int b)", "start_line": 175, "end_line": 179, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 50, "token_count": 297, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 183, "end_line": 295, "parameters": [], "filename": "3073.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 113, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3074.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 294, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39865538", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "13900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 230, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "3074.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 48, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "3074.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3075.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 328, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39816676", "exec_time": "840 ms", "memory": "11700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 35, "name": "ch", "long_name": "ch( int x , int y)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3075.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 263, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "3075.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3076.cpp", "nloc": 75, "token_count": 413, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39797823", "exec_time": "622 ms", "memory": "40400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 183, "end_line": 193, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3076.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 83, "name": "gcdExtended", "long_name": "gcdExtended( ll a , ll b , ll * x , ll * y)", "start_line": 197, "end_line": 217, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "3076.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 47, "name": "modInv", "long_name": "modInv( ll a , ll m)", "start_line": 221, "end_line": 231, "parameters": ["a", "m"], "filename": "3076.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 70, "name": "mpower", "long_name": "mpower( ll x , ll y , ll p)", "start_line": 235, "end_line": 259, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "3076.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 51, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll x , ll y)", "start_line": 263, "end_line": 281, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3076.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 285, "end_line": 367, "parameters": [], "filename": "3076.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3077.cpp", "nloc": 102, "token_count": 608, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39795540", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "14800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 8, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 57, "name": "modexpo", "long_name": "modexpo( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 53, "name": "expo", "long_name": "expo( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 91, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 89, "name": "isPrime", "long_name": "isPrime( ll n)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 121, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 53, "name": "dist", "long_name": "dist( ll x1 , ll y1 , ll x2 , ll y2)", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2"], "filename": "3077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 43, "name": "squaredist", "long_name": "squaredist( ll x1 , ll y1 , ll x2 , ll y2)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2"], "filename": "3077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 37, "name": "nCr", "long_name": "nCr( ll n , ll r)", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 151, "parameters": ["n", "r"], "filename": "3077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 233, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 183, "end_line": 267, "parameters": [], "filename": "3077.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3078.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 322, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39767144", "exec_time": "248 ms", "memory": "5400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "3078.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3079.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 389, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39147392", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "11800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 382, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "3079.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "308.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 122, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43070850", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3080.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 168, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/39014672", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "17700 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "3080.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3081.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 333, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/38816725", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "4400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 314, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "3081.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3082.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/38772349", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "12900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 187, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "3082.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3083.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 385, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/38481171", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "34500 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 288, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 64, "parameters": [], "filename": "3083.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3084.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 332, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/38086705", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "8200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "add", "long_name": "add( LL & x , LL y)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3084.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 83, "name": "Find", "long_name": "Find( int l , int r , int p , int v)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["l", "r", "p", "v"], "filename": "3084.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "3084.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3085.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/37639912", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "10100 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 195, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "3085.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3086.cpp", "nloc": 69, "token_count": 455, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/36146493", "exec_time": "372 ms", "memory": "26100 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 350, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 80, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "3086.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 46, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3087.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 343, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/35867714", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "22400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 294, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "3087.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3088.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 262, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/165/submission/35119689", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "7300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 206, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "3088.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 30, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "3088.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3089.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 308, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44115085", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 23, "name": "comparer", "long_name": "comparer( const string & a , const string & b)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3089.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 217, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "3089.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 30, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "3089.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "309.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43069608", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "309.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3090.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 245, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44090034", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 238, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "3090.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3091.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 267, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44089917", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "3091.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 69, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3092.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 280, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44089232", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 261, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "3092.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 119, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3093.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44088087", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "3093.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3094.cpp", "nloc": 136, "token_count": 873, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44087933", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "4800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 9, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 13, "macro_count": 31, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 96, "end_line": 98, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 98, "name": "isprime", "long_name": "isprime( ll n)", "start_line": 100, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 75, "name": "genPrime", "long_name": "genPrime( ll sz)", "start_line": 112, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["sz"], "filename": "3094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 66, "name": "powMod", "long_name": "powMod( ll a , ll b , ll mod)", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 138, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "3094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "modularInverse", "long_name": "modularInverse( ll a , ll mod)", "start_line": 140, "end_line": 142, "parameters": ["a", "mod"], "filename": "3094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 10, "name": "bsfunction", "long_name": "bsfunction( ll n)", "start_line": 144, "end_line": 146, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 96, "name": "binarysearch", "long_name": "binarysearch( ll left , ll right , ll target)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 162, "parameters": ["left", "right", "target"], "filename": "3094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 159, "name": "MAIN", "long_name": "MAIN()", "start_line": 168, "end_line": 193, "parameters": [], "filename": "3094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 26, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 48, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 203, "end_line": 217, "parameters": [], "filename": "3094.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3095.cpp", "nloc": 137, "token_count": 882, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44087889", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "4800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 9, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 13, "macro_count": 31, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 96, "end_line": 98, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 98, "name": "isprime", "long_name": "isprime( ll n)", "start_line": 100, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 75, "name": "genPrime", "long_name": "genPrime( ll sz)", "start_line": 112, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["sz"], "filename": "3095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 66, "name": "powMod", "long_name": "powMod( ll a , ll b , ll mod)", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 138, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "3095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "modularInverse", "long_name": "modularInverse( ll a , ll mod)", "start_line": 140, "end_line": 142, "parameters": ["a", "mod"], "filename": "3095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 10, "name": "bsfunction", "long_name": "bsfunction( ll n)", "start_line": 144, "end_line": 146, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 96, "name": "binarysearch", "long_name": "binarysearch( ll left , ll right , ll target)", "start_line": 151, "end_line": 162, "parameters": ["left", "right", "target"], "filename": "3095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 168, "name": "MAIN", "long_name": "MAIN()", "start_line": 168, "end_line": 194, "parameters": [], "filename": "3095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 48, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 204, "end_line": 218, "parameters": [], "filename": "3095.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3096.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 373, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44052665", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 18, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 256, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 36, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "3096.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3097.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 251, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44050933", "exec_time": "311 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 230, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "3097.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 32, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3098.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 355, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44048333", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 265, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "3098.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3099.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 369, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44048276", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 279, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "3099.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "31.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/44005374", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 20, "parameters": [], "filename": "31.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 16, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "310.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 182, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43069553", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "310.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3100.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 243, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/44001101", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "3100.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3101.cpp", "nloc": 62, "token_count": 428, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43997366", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 91, "name": "read", "long_name": "read( T & x)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 12, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 29, "name": "writep", "long_name": "writep( T x)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 30, "name": "write", "long_name": "write( T x)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 17, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln( T x)", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 203, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 102, "parameters": [], "filename": "3101.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 56, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3102.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 260, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43939313", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 29, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 228, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 169, "parameters": [], "filename": "3102.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3103.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 380, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43908300", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 81, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 24, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 58, "name": "binsearch", "long_name": "binsearch( ll lo , ll hi)", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["lo", "hi"], "filename": "3103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 58, "parameters": [], "filename": "3103.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3104.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 455, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43830558", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "8600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 353, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 171, "parameters": [], "filename": "3104.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3105.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 357, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43712317", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 336, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "3105.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 101, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3106.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43653793", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 224, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "3106.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 95, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3107.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 267, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43623226", "exec_time": "530 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 231, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3107.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3108.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 353, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43622359", "exec_time": "576 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 245, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "3108.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3109.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 338, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43546571", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "3400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 54, "token_count": 326, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "3109.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 111, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "311.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43067921", "exec_time": "374 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 119, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "311.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3110.cpp", "nloc": 71, "token_count": 493, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43542449", "exec_time": "155 ms", "memory": "7100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 27, "name": "c", "long_name": "c( ll i , ll j)", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["i", "j"], "filename": "3110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 134, "name": "dob", "long_name": "dob( ll y , ll i , ll j)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 113, "parameters": ["y", "i", "j"], "filename": "3110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 242, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 181, "parameters": [], "filename": "3110.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3111.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 302, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43491150", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 295, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "3111.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3112.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 285, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43485090", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 248, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "3112.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3113.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 708, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43429272", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 18, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 93, "name": "getint", "long_name": "getint()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "3113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 69, "name": "mulD", "long_name": "mulD( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 88, "name": "exp", "long_name": "exp( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 51, "name": "poww", "long_name": "poww( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 71, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( ll x , ll k , ll n)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 101, "parameters": ["x", "k", "n"], "filename": "3113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 253, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 103, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "3113.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3114.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 237, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43417698", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 197, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "3114.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3115.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43154392", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 231, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "3115.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3116.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 283, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43104914", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "12900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "3116.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 91, "name": "Can", "long_name": "Can( int b)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["b"], "filename": "3116.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3117.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 287, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43024178", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 280, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "3117.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3118.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 335, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43024090", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 49, "token_count": 328, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 52, "parameters": [], "filename": "3118.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 50, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3119.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/43019232", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "3800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 210, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "3119.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "312.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 301, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43045730", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 38, "name": "printprecise", "long_name": "printprecise( double l , ll precision)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["l", "precision"], "filename": "312.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 47, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "312.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 172, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "312.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3120.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 374, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42972024", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 39, "name": "Update", "long_name": "Update( int x , int val)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 21, "parameters": ["x", "val"], "filename": "3120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 43, "name": "Get", "long_name": "Get( int x)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 81, "name": "Enter", "long_name": "Enter()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "3120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 150, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "3120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 13, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "3120.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3121.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 312, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42971409", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 54, "name": "nhap", "long_name": "nhap()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "3121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 47, "name": "kt", "long_name": "kt( int x)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 152, "name": "xl", "long_name": "xl()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "3121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 34, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 125, "parameters": [], "filename": "3121.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3122.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 225, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42971373", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "3122.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3123.cpp", "nloc": 90, "token_count": 650, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42878880", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "EQ", "long_name": "EQ( ld a , ld b)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 59, "token_count": 417, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 167, "end_line": 287, "parameters": [], "filename": "3123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 121, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 12, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 289, "end_line": 299, "parameters": [], "filename": "3123.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3124.cpp", "nloc": 79, "token_count": 553, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42863091", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 51, "name": "PRINT", "long_name": "PRINT( T VARIABLE , string NAME)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["VARIABLE", "NAME"], "filename": "3124.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 56, "token_count": 376, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 201, "parameters": [], "filename": "3124.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 117, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3125.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42851382", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 135, "parameters": [], "filename": "3125.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 87, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3126.cpp", "nloc": 96, "token_count": 447, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42717948", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "18200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 18, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 32, "name": "show", "long_name": "show( const vector<T> & a)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "3126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 149, "end_line": 263, "parameters": [], "filename": "3126.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 115, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3127.cpp", "nloc": 63, "token_count": 623, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42717433", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "10900 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 19, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 27, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "3127.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "3127.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 47, "name": "go", "long_name": "go( ll l , ll r)", "start_line": 91, "end_line": 99, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "3127.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 423, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 185, "parameters": [], "filename": "3127.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 85, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3128.cpp", "nloc": 124, "token_count": 622, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42688588", "exec_time": "139 ms", "memory": "24600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 18, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 32, "name": "show", "long_name": "show( const vector<T> & a)", "start_line": 99, "end_line": 109, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "3128.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 34, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 155, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3128.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 68, "token_count": 353, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 321, "parameters": [], "filename": "3128.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 163, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3129.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 407, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42675872", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 58, "token_count": 400, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 159, "parameters": [], "filename": "3129.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 151, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "313.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 113, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43044731", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "313.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3130.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 351, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42554804", "exec_time": "155 ms", "memory": "1500 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 23, "name": "sum", "long_name": "sum( int a , int b)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3130.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 48, "name": "cek", "long_name": "cek( int x)", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 40, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3130.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 219, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "3130.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 38, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3131.cpp", "nloc": 70, "token_count": 479, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42547093", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "bye", "long_name": "bye()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 31, "name": "count", "long_name": "count( int l , int r)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "3131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 48, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll v)", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "3131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 88, "name": "get", "long_name": "get( ll v)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "3131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 227, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 173, "parameters": [], "filename": "3131.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3132.cpp", "nloc": 70, "token_count": 754, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42457462", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 11, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "getbit", "long_name": "getbit( T s , int i)", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 46, "parameters": ["s", "i"], "filename": "3132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "onbit", "long_name": "onbit( T s , int i)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["s", "i"], "filename": "3132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 25, "name": "offbit", "long_name": "offbit( T s , int i)", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 48, "parameters": ["s", "i"], "filename": "3132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "cntbit", "long_name": "cntbit( T s)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "3132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 42, "name": "Input", "long_name": "Input()", "start_line": 74, "end_line": 78, "parameters": [], "filename": "3132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 170, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 80, "end_line": 104, "parameters": [], "filename": "3132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 108, "end_line": 120, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "3132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 73, "name": "ControlIO", "long_name": "ControlIO( int argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 124, "end_line": 132, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "3132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "TimerStart", "long_name": "TimerStart()", "start_line": 134, "end_line": 138, "parameters": [], "filename": "3132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 45, "name": "TimerStop", "long_name": "TimerStop()", "start_line": 140, "end_line": 146, "parameters": [], "filename": "3132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 14, "name": "Exit", "long_name": "Exit()", "start_line": 148, "end_line": 150, "parameters": [], "filename": "3132.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3133.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 278, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42349665", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 271, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 48, "parameters": [], "filename": "3133.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 44, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3134.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42325180", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 215, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "3134.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3135.cpp", "nloc": 77, "token_count": 622, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42303543", "exec_time": "295 ms", "memory": "12500 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 90, "name": "print", "long_name": "print()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "3135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 106, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs( int i)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 67, "parameters": ["i"], "filename": "3135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 392, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 157, "parameters": [], "filename": "3135.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3136.cpp", "nloc": 76, "token_count": 450, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42206163", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 27, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 18, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 374, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 151, "parameters": [], "filename": "3136.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 89, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3138.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 427, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42010952", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 33, "name": "dcmp", "long_name": "dcmp( long double x , long double y)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 46, "name": "fast", "long_name": "fast()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "3138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 220, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "3138.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3139.cpp", "nloc": 72, "token_count": 719, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/42010804", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "8200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 33, "name": "dcmp", "long_name": "dcmp( long double x , long double y)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3139.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 46, "name": "fast", "long_name": "fast()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "3139.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 52, "token_count": 495, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 177, "parameters": [], "filename": "3139.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "314.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43034140", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "314.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3140.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 272, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/41945449", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 265, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 32, "parameters": [], "filename": "3140.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3141.cpp", "nloc": 79, "token_count": 417, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/41557022", "exec_time": "139 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 19, "nloc": 77, "token_count": 410, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 211, "parameters": [], "filename": "3141.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 161, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3142.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 330, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/41211740", "exec_time": "265 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "input", "long_name": "input( int n , int a [ ])", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["n", "]"], "filename": "3142.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 65, "name": "bin_expo", "long_name": "bin_expo( ll A , ll B , ll M)", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["A", "B", "M"], "filename": "3142.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "3142.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3143.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 299, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/41129785", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 290, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 52, "parameters": [], "filename": "3143.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3144.cpp", "nloc": 81, "token_count": 647, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/40984609", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 11, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 83, "name": "rl", "long_name": "rl( ll & num)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["num"], "filename": "3144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 83, "name": "ri", "long_name": "ri( int & num)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["num"], "filename": "3144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 41, "name": "getnum", "long_name": "getnum()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "3144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 47, "name": "out", "long_name": "out( int x)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 81, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 299, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 165, "parameters": [], "filename": "3144.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3145.cpp", "nloc": 90, "token_count": 524, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/40904987", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 23, "nloc": 85, "token_count": 500, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 185, "parameters": [], "filename": "3145.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 169, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3146.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/40578635", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 18, "parameters": [], "filename": "3146.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3147.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/40510353", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 222, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "3147.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3148.cpp", "nloc": 52, "token_count": 350, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/40388237", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 23, "name": "query", "long_name": "query( int l , int r)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 13, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "3148.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 54, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int x)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3148.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 243, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "3148.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3149.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 295, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/40239115", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "2300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 288, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "3149.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "315.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43034114", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "315.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3150.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 277, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/40116184", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 268, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "3150.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3151.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 341, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/39944260", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "1300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 28, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3151.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 268, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "3151.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3152.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 493, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/39879375", "exec_time": "468 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 176, "name": "busca", "long_name": "busca( int pos)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 28, "parameters": ["pos"], "filename": "3152.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 286, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "3152.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 40, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3153.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 307, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/39858462", "exec_time": "514 ms", "memory": "27700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 183, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 101, "parameters": [], "filename": "3153.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3154.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/39453538", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "3154.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3155.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 288, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/39163720", "exec_time": "217 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 270, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "3155.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3156.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 276, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/39058157", "exec_time": "295 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 244, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 71, "parameters": [], "filename": "3156.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3157.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 312, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/39042378", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 48, "token_count": 305, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "3157.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3158.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 392, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/39036192", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "6300 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 184, "name": "doit", "long_name": "doit( int b)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["b"], "filename": "3158.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "3158.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3159.cpp", "nloc": 40, "token_count": 263, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/39036050", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 245, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "3159.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "316.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 134, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43034091", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "3900 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3160.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 409, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/38598148", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "8500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 32, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "sbt", "long_name": "sbt( int x)", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 85, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "3160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 62, "name": "__f", "long_name": "__f( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 97, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "3160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 270, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 187, "parameters": [], "filename": "3160.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3161.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/38468704", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 212, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "3161.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 30, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "3161.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3162.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 424, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/38460147", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "1400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 201, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int x , int print)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["x", "print"], "filename": "3162.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 59, "name": "foo", "long_name": "foo( int l , int r)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "3162.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 123, "parameters": [], "filename": "3162.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3163.cpp", "nloc": 68, "token_count": 336, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/38449099", "exec_time": "529 ms", "memory": "4700 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 37, "name": "fx", "long_name": "fx( ll st , ll cur)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["st", "cur"], "filename": "3163.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 51, "token_count": 264, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 159, "parameters": [], "filename": "3163.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3164.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 259, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/38448847", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 218, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "3164.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3165.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 233, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/38422604", "exec_time": "295 ms", "memory": "8100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 206, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "3165.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3166.cpp", "nloc": 64, "token_count": 333, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/38127847", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "7800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 62, "token_count": 326, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 147, "parameters": [], "filename": "3166.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 129, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3167.cpp", "nloc": 79, "token_count": 401, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/38119104", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "11400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 26, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 103, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3167.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 52, "token_count": 268, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 217, "parameters": [], "filename": "3167.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 105, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3168.cpp", "nloc": 78, "token_count": 399, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/38119096", "exec_time": "311 ms", "memory": "11400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 26, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 103, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 111, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 14, "nloc": 51, "token_count": 266, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 215, "parameters": [], "filename": "3168.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3169.cpp", "nloc": 76, "token_count": 540, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/38055378", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "5600 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 21, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 31, "token_count": 292, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 40, "end_line": 70, "parameters": [], "filename": "3169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 37, "name": "choose", "long_name": "choose( ll n , ll k)", "start_line": 72, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["n", "k"], "filename": "3169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 39, "name": "isprime", "long_name": "isprime( ll n)", "start_line": 79, "end_line": 87, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 94, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 68, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( int x , int y , int p)", "start_line": 96, "end_line": 108, "parameters": ["x", "y", "p"], "filename": "3169.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "317.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43031102", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 49, "name": "can", "long_name": "can( int num)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 14, "parameters": ["num"], "filename": "317.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "317.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3170.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 278, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/37995754", "exec_time": "218 ms", "memory": "5800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 238, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "3170.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3171.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 291, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/37995632", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "5800 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 279, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "3171.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3172.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 432, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/37909763", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "6100 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "pwr", "long_name": "pwr( ll base , ll n , ll m)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["base", "n", "m"], "filename": "3172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 70, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int len)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["len"], "filename": "3172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 150, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs( int lo , int hi)", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["lo", "hi"], "filename": "3172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 139, "end_line": 167, "parameters": [], "filename": "3172.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3173.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 310, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/37908448", "exec_time": "327 ms", "memory": "4900 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 293, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "3173.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3174.cpp", "nloc": 50, "token_count": 351, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/37781834", "exec_time": "108 ms", "memory": "4400 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 274, "name": "ProblemCHardProcess::solve", "long_name": "ProblemCHardProcess::solve( std :: istream & in , std :: ostream & out)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["in", "out"], "filename": "3174.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 56, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "3174.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3175.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 252, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/37739413", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "4600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 29, "name": "Input", "long_name": "Input()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "3175.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 156, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 95, "parameters": [], "filename": "3175.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 30, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 115, "parameters": [], "filename": "3175.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3176.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 270, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/37353860", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "6800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 243, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3176.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3177.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 229, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/36665855", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 216, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "3177.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3178.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/36451150", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "3178.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3179.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 288, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/36125696", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 283, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "3179.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "318.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43031057", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 49, "name": "can", "long_name": "can( int num)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["num"], "filename": "318.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "318.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3180.cpp", "nloc": 81, "token_count": 524, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/35813957", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 58, "token_count": 425, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 92, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "3180.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3181.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 484, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/35154641", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 23, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 340, "name": "DC", "long_name": "DC( int l , int r)", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "3181.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "3181.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3182.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/34440785", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 211, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "3182.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3183.cpp", "nloc": 94, "token_count": 395, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/34096293", "exec_time": "296 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 22, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 78, "token_count": 356, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 277, "parameters": [], "filename": "3183.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 185, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3184.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 257, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/34088707", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 215, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "3184.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3185.cpp", "nloc": 119, "token_count": 586, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/34088486", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 31, "name": "suma", "long_name": "suma( int l , int r)", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 107, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "3185.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 55, "name": "good", "long_name": "good( int x)", "start_line": 111, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3185.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 73, "token_count": 364, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 283, "parameters": [], "filename": "3185.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 149, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3186.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 370, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/33856214", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 43, "token_count": 320, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "3186.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3187.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 327, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/33656841", "exec_time": "498 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 52, "token_count": 314, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "3187.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 105, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3188.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 241, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/33616242", "exec_time": "187 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 205, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "3188.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3189.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 186, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/33486318", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 157, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "3189.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "319.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 127, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43026921", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "900 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "319.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3190.cpp", "nloc": 85, "token_count": 468, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/33484497", "exec_time": "499 ms", "memory": "6200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 36, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3190.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3190.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 57, "name": "isprime", "long_name": "isprime( ll n)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 95, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3190.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 43, "name": "ispalindrome", "long_name": "ispalindrome( int n)", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 115, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3190.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 45, "token_count": 297, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 217, "parameters": [], "filename": "3190.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 93, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3191.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 328, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/32967948", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "6500 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 287, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "3191.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3192.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 289, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/32797957", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 243, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "3192.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3193.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/32780423", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "4200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "3193.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3194.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/32764579", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 165, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "3194.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3195.cpp", "nloc": 71, "token_count": 455, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/32534627", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 113, "name": "Check", "long_name": "Check( int t)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["t"], "filename": "3195.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 308, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 141, "parameters": [], "filename": "3195.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3196.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 439, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/32532989", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 95, "name": "F", "long_name": "F( int t)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["t"], "filename": "3196.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 13, "nloc": 36, "token_count": 293, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 127, "parameters": [], "filename": "3196.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 79, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3197.cpp", "nloc": 66, "token_count": 372, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/32338960", "exec_time": "139 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 15, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 153, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int k , bool pr)", "start_line": 40, "end_line": 62, "parameters": ["k", "pr"], "filename": "3197.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 119, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 65, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "3197.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3198.cpp", "nloc": 63, "token_count": 343, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/32126828", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 19, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 261, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "3198.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3199.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 318, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/32050960", "exec_time": "483 ms", "memory": "2500 KB", "usertype": "chaotic", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 16, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 311, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "3199.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 44, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "32.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43998983", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 20, "parameters": [], "filename": "32.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "320.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 129, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43026901", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "1300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "320.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3200.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 342, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/31827698", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 69, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int x)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "3200.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3201.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 325, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/31827621", "exec_time": "109 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 32, "token_count": 268, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "3201.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3202.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 253, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/31827535", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 209, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "3202.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3203.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 347, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/31622203", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "6200 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 38, "token_count": 305, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "3203.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3204.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 276, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/31586159", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 15, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "3204.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 109, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3205.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 295, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/problem/C", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/660/submission/31516701", "exec_time": "93 ms", "memory": "3100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 12, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 242, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "3205.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3206.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 330, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/submission/42814423", "exec_time": "78 ms", "memory": "4000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 142, "name": "valid", "long_name": "valid( int k)", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "3206.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 163, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "3206.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3207.cpp", "nloc": 76, "token_count": 796, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/submission/42021374", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 11, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "getbit", "long_name": "getbit( T s , int i)", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 46, "parameters": ["s", "i"], "filename": "3207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "onbit", "long_name": "onbit( T s , int i)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["s", "i"], "filename": "3207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 25, "name": "offbit", "long_name": "offbit( T s , int i)", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 48, "parameters": ["s", "i"], "filename": "3207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "cntbit", "long_name": "cntbit( T s)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "3207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 88, "name": "Input", "long_name": "Input()", "start_line": 74, "end_line": 80, "parameters": [], "filename": "3207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 160, "name": "Solve", "long_name": "Solve()", "start_line": 82, "end_line": 116, "parameters": [], "filename": "3207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 84, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 120, "end_line": 132, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "3207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 73, "name": "ControlIO", "long_name": "ControlIO( int argc , char * argv [ ])", "start_line": 136, "end_line": 144, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "3207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "TimerStart", "long_name": "TimerStart()", "start_line": 146, "end_line": 150, "parameters": [], "filename": "3207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 45, "name": "TimerStop", "long_name": "TimerStop()", "start_line": 152, "end_line": 158, "parameters": [], "filename": "3207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 14, "name": "Exit", "long_name": "Exit()", "start_line": 160, "end_line": 162, "parameters": [], "filename": "3207.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3208.cpp", "nloc": 84, "token_count": 628, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/submission/41565068", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "6400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "debug", "long_name": "debug( ostream & out , TF const & f)", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 52, "parameters": ["out", "f"], "filename": "3208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 35, "name": "debug", "long_name": "debug( ostream & out , TF const & f , TR const & ... rest)", "start_line": 58, "end_line": 64, "parameters": ["out", "f", "rest"], "filename": "3208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 57, "name": "read", "long_name": "read()", "start_line": 120, "end_line": 134, "parameters": [], "filename": "3208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 161, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int k)", "start_line": 138, "end_line": 194, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "3208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 75, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 198, "end_line": 220, "parameters": [], "filename": "3208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 30, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 224, "end_line": 238, "parameters": [], "filename": "3208.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3209.cpp", "nloc": 66, "token_count": 379, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/submission/41547901", "exec_time": "140 ms", "memory": "2700 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 190, "name": "finish", "long_name": "finish( int x)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 50, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 32, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 138, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 78, "parameters": [], "filename": "3209.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "321.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 113, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43022603", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "700 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 83, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "321.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3210.cpp", "nloc": 61, "token_count": 403, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/submission/41497088", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "5500 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "operator +", "long_name": "operator +( ii a , ii b)", "start_line": 22, "end_line": 22, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 160, "name": "cek", "long_name": "cek( int e)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 55, "parameters": ["e"], "filename": "3210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 134, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 58, "end_line": 76, "parameters": [], "filename": "3210.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3211.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 327, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/submission/41253915", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "1200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 151, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int limit)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 75, "parameters": ["limit"], "filename": "3211.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 124, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "3211.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3212.cpp", "nloc": 211, "token_count": 1483, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/submission/39044919", "exec_time": "358 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 33, "library_count": 20, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 54, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 91, "name": "readi", "long_name": "readi( int & x)", "start_line": 179, "end_line": 195, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 91, "name": "readll", "long_name": "readll( ll & x)", "start_line": 197, "end_line": 213, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 28, "name": "readc", "long_name": "readc( char & x)", "start_line": 215, "end_line": 225, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "writes", "long_name": "writes( string s)", "start_line": 227, "end_line": 227, "parameters": ["s"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 10, "name": "writeln", "long_name": "writeln()", "start_line": 229, "end_line": 229, "parameters": [], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 89, "name": "writei", "long_name": "writei( int x)", "start_line": 231, "end_line": 271, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 89, "name": "writell", "long_name": "writell( ll x)", "start_line": 273, "end_line": 313, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "inc", "long_name": "inc( int & x)", "start_line": 315, "end_line": 315, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "inc", "long_name": "inc( long long & x)", "start_line": 317, "end_line": 317, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "inc", "long_name": "inc( int & x , long long y)", "start_line": 319, "end_line": 319, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "inc", "long_name": "inc( long long & x , long long y)", "start_line": 321, "end_line": 321, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "inc", "long_name": "inc( double & x , double y)", "start_line": 323, "end_line": 323, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 12, "name": "dec", "long_name": "dec( int & x)", "start_line": 325, "end_line": 325, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 13, "name": "dec", "long_name": "dec( long long & x)", "start_line": 327, "end_line": 327, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "dec", "long_name": "dec( int & x , long long y)", "start_line": 329, "end_line": 329, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "dec", "long_name": "dec( long long & x , long long y)", "start_line": 331, "end_line": 331, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "dec", "long_name": "dec( double & x , double y)", "start_line": 333, "end_line": 333, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( int & x)", "start_line": 335, "end_line": 335, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( long long & x)", "start_line": 337, "end_line": 337, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( int & x , long long y)", "start_line": 339, "end_line": 339, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( long long & x , long long y)", "start_line": 341, "end_line": 341, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "mul", "long_name": "mul( double & x , double y)", "start_line": 343, "end_line": 343, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 77, "name": "divi", "long_name": "divi( const int & x)", "start_line": 345, "end_line": 375, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 78, "name": "divi", "long_name": "divi( const long long & x)", "start_line": 377, "end_line": 407, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "divi", "long_name": "divi( int & x , long long y)", "start_line": 409, "end_line": 409, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "divi", "long_name": "divi( long long & x , long long y)", "start_line": 411, "end_line": 411, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "divi", "long_name": "divi( double & x , double y)", "start_line": 413, "end_line": 413, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod( int & x , long long y)", "start_line": 415, "end_line": 415, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 19, "name": "mod", "long_name": "mod( long long & x , long long y)", "start_line": 417, "end_line": 417, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 19, "name": "cmpid", "long_name": "cmpid( tst x , tst y)", "start_line": 505, "end_line": 511, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 19, "name": "cmplst", "long_name": "cmplst( tst x , tst y)", "start_line": 513, "end_line": 519, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 246, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int x)", "start_line": 521, "end_line": 585, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 135, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 587, "end_line": 633, "parameters": [], "filename": "3212.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3213.cpp", "nloc": 45, "token_count": 315, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/submission/38786503", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "4600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 97, "name": "itWorks", "long_name": "itWorks( int pos)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["pos"], "filename": "3213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "3213.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3214.cpp", "nloc": 39, "token_count": 408, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/problem/D", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/732/submission/38770249", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "chkmax", "long_name": "chkmax( T & x , T y)", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "chkmin", "long_name": "chkmin( T & x , T y)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 166, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int k)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "3214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 109, "parameters": [], "filename": "3214.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3215.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 382, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44060231", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 58, "name": "lgput", "long_name": "lgput( ll a , ll b , ll mod)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "3215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 78, "name": "binarySearch", "long_name": "binarySearch( vector<int> & v , int value)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["v", "value"], "filename": "3215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( ll x , ll MOD)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["x", "MOD"], "filename": "3215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "3215.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3216.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 527, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44041906", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 13, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 28, "name": "fastIO", "long_name": "fastIO()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "mnze", "long_name": "mnze( T & x , U y)", "start_line": 36, "end_line": 36, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "mxze", "long_name": "mxze( T & x , U y)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "_scan", "long_name": "_scan( int & x)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "_scan", "long_name": "_scan( long long & x)", "start_line": 40, "end_line": 40, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "_scan", "long_name": "_scan( double & x)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "_scan", "long_name": "_scan( char & x)", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 42, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "_scan", "long_name": "_scan( char * x)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 5, "name": "scan", "long_name": "scan()", "start_line": 44, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "scan", "long_name": "scan( T & head , U & ... tail)", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 46, "parameters": ["head", "tail"], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "_dbg", "long_name": "_dbg( const char * sdbg , T h)", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 48, "parameters": ["sdbg", "h"], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 51, "name": "_dbg", "long_name": "_dbg( const char * sdbg , T h , U ... t)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 52, "parameters": ["sdbg", "h", "t"], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 74, "end_line": 94, "parameters": [], "filename": "3216.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3217.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44015188", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "3217.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3218.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44014791", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "3218.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3219.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 123, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43981463", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 104, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "3219.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "322.cpp", "nloc": 68, "token_count": 315, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43011915", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 22, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 168, "name": "Solution::solve", "long_name": "Solution::solve( std :: istream & in , std :: ostream & out)", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 137, "parameters": ["in", "out"], "filename": "322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 41, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( std :: istream & in , std :: ostream & out)", "start_line": 143, "end_line": 153, "parameters": ["in", "out"], "filename": "322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 41, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 185, "parameters": [], "filename": "322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3220.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43911620", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "CocaCola", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 161, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "3220.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3221.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 417, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43911385", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 12, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "cww::cww", "long_name": "cww::cww()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "chmin", "long_name": "chmin( T & l , T r)", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 35, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 29, "name": "chmax", "long_name": "chmax( T & l , T r)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["l", "r"], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 33, "name": "operator > >", "long_name": "operator > >( istream & is , vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["is", "v"], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 9, "name": "range::I::operator *", "long_name": "range::I::operator *()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 2, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "range::I::operator !=", "long_name": "range::I::operator !=( I & lhs)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["lhs"], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 2, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 9, "name": "range::I::operator ++", "long_name": "range::I::operator ++()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 2, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "range::range", "long_name": "range::range( int n)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "range::range", "long_name": "range::range( int i , int n)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["i", "n"], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 8, "name": "range::begin", "long_name": "range::begin()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 8, "name": "range::end", "long_name": "range::end()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 141, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "3221.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3222.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43903506", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "root_paradox", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 36, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 18, "end_line": 22, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 58, "parameters": [], "filename": "3222.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3223.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43903428", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 117, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "3223.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3224.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 179, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43803132", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 25, "parameters": [], "filename": "3224.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3225.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 116, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43749467", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 96, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "3225.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3226.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 200, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43735966", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "ASK", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 193, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 117, "parameters": [], "filename": "3226.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 91, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3227.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 233, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43733797", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 196, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "3227.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3228.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43716407", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "3228.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3229.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43713345", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "3229.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "323.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/43002496", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "323.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3230.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 256, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43703343", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Harem++", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 42, "token_count": 249, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "3230.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 83, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3231.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43697638", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 186, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 111, "parameters": [], "filename": "3231.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3232.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 136, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43684260", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 124, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 41, "parameters": [], "filename": "3232.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3233.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 141, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43679201", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "random", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 4, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "3233.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3234.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 135, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43674170", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 124, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 24, "parameters": [], "filename": "3234.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 18, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3235.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43674086", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Masti_Ki_Pathshala", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 27, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 158, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "3235.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 51, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3236.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 603, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43662356", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 7, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 36, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 125, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "is_vowel", "long_name": "is_vowel( char c)", "start_line": 127, "end_line": 127, "parameters": ["c"], "filename": "3236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 66, "name": "extended_euclidean", "long_name": "extended_euclidean( ll a , ll b , ll & x , ll & y)", "start_line": 129, "end_line": 129, "parameters": ["a", "b", "x", "y"], "filename": "3236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 68, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( ll base , ll p , ll mod)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["base", "p", "mod"], "filename": "3236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 56, "name": "Trianglearea", "long_name": "Trianglearea( int x1 , int y1 , int x2 , int y2 , int x3 , int y3)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2", "x3", "y3"], "filename": "3236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 198, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 207, "parameters": [], "filename": "3236.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3237.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 288, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43660348", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "kuhaku", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 37, "token_count": 260, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 105, "parameters": [], "filename": "3237.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3239.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 402, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43639259", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Grey", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 31, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 38, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , pair<S,T> const & p)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["out", "p"], "filename": "3239.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 73, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , vector<T> const & v)", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["out", "v"], "filename": "3239.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 27, "name": "trace", "long_name": "trace( const char * name , T && arg1)", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 46, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "3239.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 62, "name": "trace", "long_name": "trace( const char * names , T && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 50, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "3239.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 2, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 162, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 52, "end_line": 76, "parameters": [], "filename": "3239.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "324.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 273, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42982735", "exec_time": "248 ms", "memory": "4300 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 87, "name": "slidingWindow", "long_name": "slidingWindow()", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "324.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 47, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 77, "end_line": 91, "parameters": [], "filename": "324.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3240.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 100, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43620333", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 93, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "3240.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3241.cpp", "nloc": 21, "token_count": 132, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43612105", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbies", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "3241.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3242.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 108, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43610621", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 101, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "3242.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3243.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43610564", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 4, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "Abs", "long_name": "Abs( lint x)", "start_line": 51, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3243.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "3243.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3244.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 157, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43596409", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 142, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "3244.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3245.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 224, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43594661", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "3245.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3246.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43590910", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "3246.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3247.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 175, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43574944", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 9, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 146, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 57, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "3247.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3248.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 119, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43568706", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 112, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "3248.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3249.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 212, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43568251", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 189, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "3249.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "325.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42967322", "exec_time": "342 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 132, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "325.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3250.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 230, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43566864", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 185, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "3250.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 20, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3251.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 128, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43538553", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "3251.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3252.cpp", "nloc": 58, "token_count": 394, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43509418", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 136, "name": "LinearSolve", "long_name": "LinearSolve()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "3252.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 45, "name": "needed", "long_name": "needed( int x)", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 83, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3252.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 104, "name": "LogSolve", "long_name": "LogSolve()", "start_line": 87, "end_line": 121, "parameters": [], "filename": "3252.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 73, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 125, "end_line": 145, "parameters": [], "filename": "3252.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3253.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 225, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43502058", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 10, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "3253.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3254.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/43488418", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "15700 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "3254.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3255.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 124, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/44041307", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 21, "parameters": [], "filename": "3255.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3256.cpp", "nloc": 28, "token_count": 217, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/44029414", "exec_time": "436 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 12, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 118, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "3256.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3257.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 124, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/43875672", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "3257.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3258.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/43522302", "exec_time": "436 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 221, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "3258.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3259.cpp", "nloc": 57, "token_count": 414, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/42723035", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 82, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( ll x)", "start_line": 113, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3259.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 129, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 139, "end_line": 213, "parameters": [], "filename": "3259.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "326.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 161, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42965560", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "326.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3260.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 215, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/42663395", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "200 KB", "usertype": "International", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 14, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 156, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 99, "parameters": [], "filename": "3260.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3261.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/41739607", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 149, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "3261.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3262.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 110, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/41658144", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 100, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "3262.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3263.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/40861152", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 168, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 69, "parameters": [], "filename": "3263.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3264.cpp", "nloc": 293, "token_count": 2368, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/40750101", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 47, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 4, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 23, "name": "seti::seti", "long_name": "seti::seti()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 17, "parameters": [], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 44, "name": "seti::seti", "long_name": "seti::seti( initializer_list<T> o)", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 18, "name": "seti::operator [ ]", "long_name": "seti::operator [ ]( int i)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["i"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "vectori::vectori", "long_name": "vectori::vectori( size_t n , T e = T())", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["n", "T"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 20, "name": "vectori::vectori", "long_name": "vectori::vectori( InputIt first , InputIt last)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["first", "last"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "vectori::vectori", "long_name": "vectori::vectori( initializer_list<T> o)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 47, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 15, "name": "vectori::operator +=", "long_name": "vectori::operator +=( T o)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 34, "name": "vectori::operator +=", "long_name": "vectori::operator +=( initializer_list<T> o)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 34, "name": "vectori::operator +=", "long_name": "vectori::operator +=( vectori<T> o)", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 64, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const vector<T> & arr)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["out", "arr"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 64, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const vectori<T> & arr)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["out", "arr"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 76, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const map<T,P> & arr)", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 169, "parameters": ["out", "arr"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 66, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const set<T,P> & arr)", "start_line": 175, "end_line": 203, "parameters": ["out", "arr"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 64, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const seti<T> & arr)", "start_line": 209, "end_line": 237, "parameters": ["out", "arr"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "__debugg", "long_name": "__debugg( const char * name , Arg1 && arg1)", "start_line": 245, "end_line": 249, "parameters": ["name", "arg1"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 76, "name": "__debugg", "long_name": "__debugg( const char * names , Arg1 && arg1 , Args && ... args)", "start_line": 253, "end_line": 269, "parameters": ["names", "arg1", "args"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "Pair::Pair", "long_name": "Pair::Pair( const X1 & x , const Y1 & y)", "start_line": 289, "end_line": 289, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 5, "name": "Pair::Pair", "long_name": "Pair::Pair()", "start_line": 291, "end_line": 291, "parameters": [], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "Pair::Pair", "long_name": "Pair::Pair( const X1 & x)", "start_line": 295, "end_line": 295, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 37, "name": "Pair::operator +", "long_name": "Pair::operator +( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 299, "end_line": 303, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 37, "name": "Pair::operator -", "long_name": "Pair::operator -( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 307, "end_line": 311, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 37, "name": "Pair::operator *", "long_name": "Pair::operator *( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 315, "end_line": 319, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 37, "name": "Pair::operator /", "long_name": "Pair::operator /( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 323, "end_line": 327, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 27, "name": "Pair::operator +=", "long_name": "Pair::operator +=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o)", "start_line": 331, "end_line": 337, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 27, "name": "Pair::operator -=", "long_name": "Pair::operator -=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o)", "start_line": 341, "end_line": 347, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 27, "name": "Pair::operator *=", "long_name": "Pair::operator *=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o)", "start_line": 351, "end_line": 357, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 27, "name": "Pair::operator /=", "long_name": "Pair::operator /=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o)", "start_line": 361, "end_line": 367, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 38, "name": "Pair::operator <", "long_name": "Pair::operator <( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 371, "end_line": 381, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 38, "name": "Pair::operator <=", "long_name": "Pair::operator <=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 385, "end_line": 395, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 38, "name": "Pair::operator >", "long_name": "Pair::operator >( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 399, "end_line": 409, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 38, "name": "Pair::operator >=", "long_name": "Pair::operator >=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 413, "end_line": 423, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "Pair::operator ==", "long_name": "Pair::operator ==( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 427, "end_line": 431, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 29, "name": "Pair::operator !=", "long_name": "Pair::operator !=( const Pair<X1,Y1> & o) const", "start_line": 435, "end_line": 439, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 31, "name": "Pair::swap", "long_name": "Pair::swap( Pair<X1,Y1> & o)", "start_line": 443, "end_line": 449, "parameters": ["o"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 27, "name": "makep", "long_name": "makep( const X & x , const Y & y)", "start_line": 457, "end_line": 461, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 44, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & out , const Pair<X,Y> & p)", "start_line": 467, "end_line": 473, "parameters": ["out", "p"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 34, "name": "operator > >", "long_name": "operator > >( istream & in , Pair<X,Y> & p)", "start_line": 479, "end_line": 485, "parameters": ["in", "p"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 35, "name": "operator > >", "long_name": "operator > >( istream & in , vector<T> & arr)", "start_line": 515, "end_line": 527, "parameters": ["in", "arr"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 13, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 47, "name": "printi", "long_name": "printi( const T & arr , char skyr = '\\n')", "start_line": 533, "end_line": 553, "parameters": ["arr", "'\\n'"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 47, "name": "printi", "long_name": "printi( const T & arr , const string & skyr)", "start_line": 559, "end_line": 579, "parameters": ["arr", "skyr"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 34, "name": "printp", "long_name": "printp( const Pair<X,Y> & p , char skyr = ' ')", "start_line": 585, "end_line": 589, "parameters": ["p", "' '"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 34, "name": "printp", "long_name": "printp( const Pair<X,Y> & p , const string & skyr)", "start_line": 597, "end_line": 601, "parameters": ["p", "skyr"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "mini", "long_name": "mini( X & a , const Y & b)", "start_line": 611, "end_line": 621, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 26, "name": "maxi", "long_name": "maxi( X & a , const Y & b)", "start_line": 629, "end_line": 639, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "between", "long_name": "between( ll v)", "start_line": 649, "end_line": 653, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 28, "name": "between", "long_name": "between( ll X , ll v , ll Y)", "start_line": 659, "end_line": 663, "parameters": ["X", "v", "Y"], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 693, "end_line": 739, "parameters": [], "filename": "3264.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3265.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 194, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/40241729", "exec_time": "122 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 153, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 113, "parameters": [], "filename": "3265.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3266.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/38932877", "exec_time": "436 ms", "memory": "4100 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 44, "name": "upfile", "long_name": "upfile()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "3266.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 81, "parameters": [], "filename": "3266.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3267.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 111, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/38893655", "exec_time": "404 ms", "memory": "3300 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 87, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 33, "parameters": [], "filename": "3267.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3268.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/38584418", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 59, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int k)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["k"], "filename": "3268.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 51, "name": "binsearch", "long_name": "binsearch( int lo , int hi)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 71, "parameters": ["lo", "hi"], "filename": "3268.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 52, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "3268.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3269.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 117, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/38584379", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 89, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "3269.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "327.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 240, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42964508", "exec_time": "310 ms", "memory": "1100 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 233, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "327.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3270.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/38061111", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "3600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 44, "name": "process", "long_name": "process( long long val)", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 29, "parameters": ["val"], "filename": "3270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 111, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 63, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "3270.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3271.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/37892817", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "3700 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 13, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 59, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "3271.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3272.cpp", "nloc": 13, "token_count": 96, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/35756444", "exec_time": "436 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 78, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 27, "parameters": [], "filename": "3272.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3273.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 188, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/35756236", "exec_time": "124 ms", "memory": "2400 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 175, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "3273.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3274.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 207, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/35756115", "exec_time": "122 ms", "memory": "2800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "chkmax", "long_name": "chkmax( T & x , U y)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "chkmin", "long_name": "chkmin( T & x , U y)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 103, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "3274.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3275.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/35753880", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "2800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 119, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "3275.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3276.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 140, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/35753788", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "2800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 122, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3276.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3277.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 157, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/35731784", "exec_time": "622 ms", "memory": "2900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 133, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "3277.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3279.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/35127163", "exec_time": "436 ms", "memory": "2200 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 70, "name": "enough", "long_name": "enough( long long rounds)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["rounds"], "filename": "3279.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 35, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "3279.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "328.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42963364", "exec_time": "122 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "328.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3280.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 104, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/34476890", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "2000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 97, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "3280.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3281.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 177, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/34161577", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "2600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "3281.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3282.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/33236136", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "2800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 77, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve( int v)", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "3282.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "3282.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3283.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 105, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/33071953", "exec_time": "404 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 98, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 43, "parameters": [], "filename": "3283.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3284.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 192, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/33017048", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "2800 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 45, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( LL mid , int n)", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["mid", "n"], "filename": "3284.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char const * argv [ ])", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 61, "parameters": ["argc", "]"], "filename": "3284.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3285.cpp", "nloc": 15, "token_count": 100, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/33007864", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "1800 KB", "usertype": "Grandmaster", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 93, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 31, "parameters": [], "filename": "3285.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3286.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 144, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/32987211", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "5000 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 74, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "3286.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3287.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 110, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/32986789", "exec_time": "560 ms", "memory": "1900 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 15, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 86, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 57, "end_line": 83, "parameters": [], "filename": "3287.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3288.cpp", "nloc": 12, "token_count": 127, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/32917969", "exec_time": "62 ms", "memory": "3600 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 14, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 79, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 55, "parameters": [], "filename": "3288.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3289.cpp", "nloc": 41, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/348/submission/32530188", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 30, "name": "f", "long_name": "f( LL add)", "start_line": 14, "end_line": 17, "parameters": ["add"], "filename": "3289.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 192, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "3289.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "329.cpp", "nloc": 46, "token_count": 206, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42959244", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "1600 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 44, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 103, "parameters": [], "filename": "329.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 97, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3290.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 196, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44167212", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 52, "name": "cal", "long_name": "cal()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "3290.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 123, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "3290.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3291.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 197, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44163861", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 190, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 75, "parameters": [], "filename": "3291.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3292.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 164, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44151708", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "3292.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3293.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 247, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44117268", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 3, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 10, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 34, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3293.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3293.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "3293.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3294.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 239, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44117079", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 41, "token_count": 232, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "3294.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 103, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3295.cpp", "nloc": 47, "token_count": 425, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44108935", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 5, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 42, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 58, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( T a , T b)", "start_line": 115, "end_line": 117, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3295.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 2, "token_count": 54, "name": "lcm", "long_name": "lcm( T a , T b)", "start_line": 119, "end_line": 121, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3295.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "power", "long_name": "power( T N , T P)", "start_line": 123, "end_line": 123, "parameters": ["N", "P"], "filename": "3295.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 22, "name": "debugger::operator ,", "long_name": "debugger::operator ,( const T & v)", "start_line": 155, "end_line": 161, "parameters": ["v"], "filename": "3295.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 150, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 169, "end_line": 229, "parameters": [], "filename": "3295.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 61, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3296.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 169, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44104949", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 20, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 89, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "3296.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 41, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3297.cpp", "nloc": 135, "token_count": 678, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44097643", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 14, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 14, "name": "Heap::LeftChildIndex", "long_name": "Heap::LeftChildIndex( int index)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["index"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 14, "name": "Heap::RightChildIndex", "long_name": "Heap::RightChildIndex( int index)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 49, "parameters": ["index"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 16, "name": "Heap::ParentIndex", "long_name": "Heap::ParentIndex( int index)", "start_line": 53, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["index"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 18, "name": "Heap::HasLeftChild", "long_name": "Heap::HasLeftChild( int index)", "start_line": 63, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["index"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 18, "name": "Heap::HasRightChild", "long_name": "Heap::HasRightChild( int index)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 79, "parameters": ["index"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 11, "name": "Heap::GetMin", "long_name": "Heap::GetMin()", "start_line": 83, "end_line": 89, "parameters": [], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 24, "name": "Heap::Add", "long_name": "Heap::Add( int newValue)", "start_line": 93, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["newValue"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 69, "name": "Heap::Remove", "long_name": "Heap::Remove( int newValue)", "start_line": 107, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["newValue"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 48, "name": "Heap::HeapifyUp", "long_name": "Heap::HeapifyUp( int index)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 157, "parameters": ["index"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 84, "name": "Heap::HeapifyDown", "long_name": "Heap::HeapifyDown( int index)", "start_line": 161, "end_line": 193, "parameters": ["index"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 35, "name": "Heap::swap", "long_name": "Heap::swap( int i1 , int i2)", "start_line": 197, "end_line": 207, "parameters": ["i1", "i2"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 103, "name": "sort", "long_name": "sort( vector<int> & a)", "start_line": 213, "end_line": 249, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 72, "name": "resort", "long_name": "resort( vector<int> & a)", "start_line": 253, "end_line": 277, "parameters": ["a"], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 106, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 281, "end_line": 329, "parameters": [], "filename": "3297.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3298.cpp", "nloc": 42, "token_count": 219, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44096053", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "3298.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3299.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44096050", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 8, "nloc": 40, "token_count": 212, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 87, "parameters": [], "filename": "3299.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "33.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/492/submission/43995830", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "33.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 71, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "330.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42917093", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "330.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3300.cpp", "nloc": 60, "token_count": 682, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44092412", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 8, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 34, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 30, "name": "isLeap", "long_name": "isLeap( T y)", "start_line": 131, "end_line": 131, "parameters": ["y"], "filename": "3300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 62, "name": "BIGMOD", "long_name": "BIGMOD( T A , T B , T M = MOD)", "start_line": 133, "end_line": 133, "parameters": ["A", "B", "MOD"], "filename": "3300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 60, "name": "BigMod", "long_name": "BigMod( T A , T B , T M)", "start_line": 135, "end_line": 135, "parameters": ["A", "B", "M"], "filename": "3300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 54, "name": "MySqrt", "long_name": "MySqrt( lld n)", "start_line": 137, "end_line": 137, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 61, "name": "MyPow", "long_name": "MyPow( lld x , lld n)", "start_line": 139, "end_line": 139, "parameters": ["x", "n"], "filename": "3300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "modInverse", "long_name": "modInverse( lld n)", "start_line": 141, "end_line": 141, "parameters": ["n"], "filename": "3300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 8, "name": "bye", "long_name": "bye()", "start_line": 145, "end_line": 151, "parameters": [], "filename": "3300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 46, "token_count": 261, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 159, "end_line": 279, "parameters": [], "filename": "3300.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 121, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3301.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44092146", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "3301.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3302.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44092118", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "3302.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3303.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 187, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44092089", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 27, "token_count": 180, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "3303.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3304.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 269, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44091627", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 27, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 5, "token_count": 56, "name": "pointPos", "long_name": "pointPos( ll x1 , ll y1 , ll x2 , ll y2 , ll x3 , ll y3)", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 89, "parameters": ["x1", "y1", "x2", "y2", "x3", "y3"], "filename": "3304.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 35, "token_count": 199, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 101, "end_line": 181, "parameters": [], "filename": "3304.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 81, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3305.cpp", "nloc": 36, "token_count": 228, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44091363", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 115, "name": "bs", "long_name": "bs()", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "3305.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 94, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 69, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "3305.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3306.cpp", "nloc": 55, "token_count": 299, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44090950", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 6, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 17, "name": "DESC", "long_name": "DESC( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3306.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 22, "name": "max", "long_name": "max( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3306.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 22, "name": "min", "long_name": "min( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 65, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3306.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 30, "name": "bmm", "long_name": "bmm( ll a , ll b)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 73, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3306.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 38, "name": "roof", "long_name": "roof( double a , double b)", "start_line": 75, "end_line": 85, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3306.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 97, "end_line": 155, "parameters": [], "filename": "3306.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3307.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 149, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44090538", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 3, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 13, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 49, "parameters": [], "filename": "3307.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3308.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 624, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44089812", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 12, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 8, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 18, "name": "sz", "long_name": "sz( T & x)", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 24, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "show", "long_name": "show( T first)", "start_line": 25, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["first"], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "sort_fun", "long_name": "sort_fun( T a , T b)", "start_line": 26, "end_line": 26, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 31, "name": "found", "long_name": "found( T t , U u)", "start_line": 27, "end_line": 27, "parameters": ["t", "u"], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 22, "name": "show", "long_name": "show( T first , Args ... args)", "start_line": 30, "end_line": 30, "parameters": ["first", "args"], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 38, "name": "_p", "long_name": "_p( T x)", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 41, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & o , pair<T,U> & x)", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 32, "parameters": ["o", "x"], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , vector<T> & x)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 33, "parameters": ["os", "x"], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 35, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , set<T> & x)", "start_line": 34, "end_line": 34, "parameters": ["os", "x"], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "Desc::operator ( )", "long_name": "Desc::operator ( )( int a , int b)", "start_line": 38, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 1, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 143, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 62, "parameters": [], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 64, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 64, "end_line": 74, "parameters": [], "filename": "3308.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3309.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44089278", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 202, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 93, "parameters": [], "filename": "3309.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 75, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "331.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 213, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42917048", "exec_time": "92 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 42, "parameters": [], "filename": "331.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 36, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3310.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 235, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44088502", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 222, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "3310.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3311.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 167, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44081434", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 9, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 160, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "3311.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3312.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44078922", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 176, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "3312.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 43, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3313.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 423, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44078596", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 93, "name": "gi", "long_name": "gi()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 16, "parameters": [], "filename": "3313.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 93, "name": "gl", "long_name": "gl()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "3313.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 55, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int mid)", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "3313.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "3313.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3314.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 170, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44078562", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 128, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "3314.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 33, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3315.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44072546", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3315.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3316.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 153, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44072553", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3316.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3317.cpp", "nloc": 18, "token_count": 139, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44071626", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 115, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "3317.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3318.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 174, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44071466", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 145, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 8, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "3318.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3319.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 423, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44069787", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 93, "name": "gi", "long_name": "gi()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 16, "parameters": [], "filename": "3319.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 6, "token_count": 93, "name": "gl", "long_name": "gl()", "start_line": 17, "end_line": 22, "parameters": [], "filename": "3319.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 6, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 55, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int mid)", "start_line": 24, "end_line": 31, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "3319.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 8, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 32, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "3319.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 14, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3320.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 396, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44067087", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 17, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 70, "name": "pwr", "long_name": "pwr( int base , int p)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 45, "parameters": ["base", "p"], "filename": "3320.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 29, "name": "gcd", "long_name": "gcd( int a , int b)", "start_line": 47, "end_line": 53, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3320.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 50, "name": "powr", "long_name": "powr( int base , int p)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["base", "p"], "filename": "3320.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 71, "end_line": 119, "parameters": [], "filename": "3320.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3321.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 178, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44065177", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 169, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 65, "parameters": [], "filename": "3321.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 55, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3322.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 166, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44065042", "exec_time": "30 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 4, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 61, "parameters": [], "filename": "3322.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3323.cpp", "nloc": 49, "token_count": 276, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44062763", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 47, "token_count": 269, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 107, "parameters": [], "filename": "3323.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 99, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3324.cpp", "nloc": 19, "token_count": 137, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44061741", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 120, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "3324.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3325.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 232, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44060390", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "500 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 8, "token_count": 55, "name": "check", "long_name": "check( int mid)", "start_line": 45, "end_line": 59, "parameters": ["mid"], "filename": "3325.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 106, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 61, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "3325.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 17, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3326.cpp", "nloc": 51, "token_count": 382, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44060231", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 4, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 2, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 58, "name": "lgput", "long_name": "lgput( ll a , ll b , ll mod)", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["a", "b", "mod"], "filename": "3326.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 78, "name": "binarySearch", "long_name": "binarySearch( vector<int> & v , int value)", "start_line": 55, "end_line": 69, "parameters": ["v", "value"], "filename": "3326.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 15, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 22, "name": "inv", "long_name": "inv( ll x , ll MOD)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["x", "MOD"], "filename": "3326.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 5, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 147, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 81, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "3326.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3327.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44060048", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 34, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "3327.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3328.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44057560", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 10, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 13, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 125, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( void)", "start_line": 73, "end_line": 103, "parameters": ["void"], "filename": "3328.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3329.cpp", "nloc": 31, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44054206", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 182, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "3329.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 73, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "333.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 137, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42913882", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "600 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 130, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 45, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3330.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44054088", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 170, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 47, "parameters": [], "filename": "3330.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3331.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 180, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44051574", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 15, "end_line": 51, "parameters": [], "filename": "3331.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3332.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44051409", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 16, "end_line": 37, "parameters": [], "filename": "3332.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 22, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3333.cpp", "nloc": 30, "token_count": 261, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44047955", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 6, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 11, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 215, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 29, "end_line": 77, "parameters": [], "filename": "3333.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 49, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3334.cpp", "nloc": 35, "token_count": 255, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44046478", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 10, "nloc": 33, "token_count": 248, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "3334.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 67, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3335.cpp", "nloc": 37, "token_count": 209, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44046426", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 188, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3336.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 189, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44045747", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 85, "parameters": [], "filename": "3336.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 77, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3337.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44043720", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 6, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "3337.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 37, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3338.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 193, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44043461", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 11, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 178, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 33, "end_line": 97, "parameters": [], "filename": "3338.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 65, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3339.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 161, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44043382", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 154, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "3339.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "334.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 191, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42909263", "exec_time": "156 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 173, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 9, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "334.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 59, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3340.cpp", "nloc": 25, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44042683", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 23, "token_count": 164, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 28, "parameters": [], "filename": "3340.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 23, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3341.cpp", "nloc": 56, "token_count": 527, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44041906", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "100 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 13, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 16, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 3, "token_count": 28, "name": "fastIO", "long_name": "fastIO()", "start_line": 21, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 3, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "mnze", "long_name": "mnze( T & x , U y)", "start_line": 36, "end_line": 36, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 21, "name": "mxze", "long_name": "mxze( T & x , U y)", "start_line": 37, "end_line": 37, "parameters": ["x", "y"], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "_scan", "long_name": "_scan( int & x)", "start_line": 39, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 17, "name": "_scan", "long_name": "_scan( long long & x)", "start_line": 40, "end_line": 40, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "_scan", "long_name": "_scan( double & x)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 41, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 16, "name": "_scan", "long_name": "_scan( char & x)", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 42, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 15, "name": "_scan", "long_name": "_scan( char * x)", "start_line": 43, "end_line": 43, "parameters": ["x"], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 5, "name": "scan", "long_name": "scan()", "start_line": 44, "end_line": 44, "parameters": [], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 24, "name": "scan", "long_name": "scan( T & head , U & ... tail)", "start_line": 46, "end_line": 46, "parameters": ["head", "tail"], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 1, "token_count": 26, "name": "_dbg", "long_name": "_dbg( const char * sdbg , T h)", "start_line": 48, "end_line": 48, "parameters": ["sdbg", "h"], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 1, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 51, "name": "_dbg", "long_name": "_dbg( const char * sdbg , T h , U ... t)", "start_line": 49, "end_line": 52, "parameters": ["sdbg", "h", "t"], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 74, "end_line": 94, "parameters": [], "filename": "3341.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3342.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 201, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44041828", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 9, "nloc": 22, "token_count": 194, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 53, "parameters": [], "filename": "3342.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3343.cpp", "nloc": 38, "token_count": 185, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44040902", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 8, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 159, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 23, "end_line": 79, "parameters": [], "filename": "3343.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3344.cpp", "nloc": 14, "token_count": 118, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44040236", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 10, "token_count": 97, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 15, "parameters": [], "filename": "3344.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 10, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3345.cpp", "nloc": 43, "token_count": 195, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44039024", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 12, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 28, "token_count": 155, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 19, "end_line": 46, "parameters": [], "filename": "3345.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 28, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3346.cpp", "nloc": 33, "token_count": 160, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44030580", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 6, "nloc": 30, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 73, "parameters": [], "filename": "3346.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 63, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3347.cpp", "nloc": 29, "token_count": 171, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44029072", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 5, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 15, "name": "cmp", "long_name": "cmp( int a , int b)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 10, "parameters": ["a", "b"], "filename": "3347.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 19, "token_count": 140, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "3347.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3348.cpp", "nloc": 23, "token_count": 140, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44028234", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 127, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "3348.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 53, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3349.cpp", "nloc": 34, "token_count": 176, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44027196", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "300 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 7, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 1, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 24, "token_count": 143, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 12, "end_line": 38, "parameters": [], "filename": "3349.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 27, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "335.cpp", "nloc": 17, "token_count": 117, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42896825", "exec_time": "280 ms", "memory": "400 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 16, "token_count": 114, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 35, "parameters": [], "filename": "335.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 31, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3350.cpp", "nloc": 16, "token_count": 127, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44018338", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Expert", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 7, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 12, "token_count": 109, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 31, "end_line": 59, "parameters": [], "filename": "3350.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 29, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3351.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 154, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44015188", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Master", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 136, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 30, "parameters": [], "filename": "3351.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3352.cpp", "nloc": 24, "token_count": 190, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44014791", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Candidate", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 177, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 67, "parameters": [], "filename": "3352.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3353.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44011448", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Newbie", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 17, "token_count": 174, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 45, "parameters": [], "filename": "3353.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 39, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3354.cpp", "nloc": 44, "token_count": 358, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44010711", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 2, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 3, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 26, "token_count": 241, "name": "CalculateMinAndMax", "long_name": "CalculateMinAndMax( const std :: vector<int> & benches , int m , int & min , int & max)", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 39, "parameters": ["benches", "m", "min", "max"], "filename": "3354.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 34, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 15, "token_count": 109, "name": "main", "long_name": "main( int argc , char ** argv)", "start_line": 42, "end_line": 62, "parameters": ["argc", "argv"], "filename": "3354.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3355.cpp", "nloc": 20, "token_count": 114, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44008666", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 18, "token_count": 107, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 39, "parameters": [], "filename": "3355.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 35, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3356.cpp", "nloc": 129, "token_count": 812, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44007139", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 10, "library_count": 2, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 5, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 28, "name": "_dbg", "long_name": "_dbg( char const * s , const T & t)", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 10, "parameters": ["s", "t"], "filename": "3356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 7, "token_count": 55, "name": "_dbg", "long_name": "_dbg( char const * s , const T & t , const TA & ... ta)", "start_line": 13, "end_line": 19, "parameters": ["s", "t", "ta"], "filename": "3356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 7, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 1, "nloc": 4, "token_count": 42, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const pair<T1,T2> & p)", "start_line": 22, "end_line": 25, "parameters": ["os", "p"], "filename": "3356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 4, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 74, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const vector<T> & v)", "start_line": 28, "end_line": 38, "parameters": ["os", "v"], "filename": "3356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 76, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const map<T1,T2> & mp)", "start_line": 41, "end_line": 51, "parameters": ["os", "mp"], "filename": "3356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 74, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const set<T> & s)", "start_line": 54, "end_line": 64, "parameters": ["os", "s"], "filename": "3356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 11, "token_count": 74, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const multiset<T> & s)", "start_line": 67, "end_line": 77, "parameters": ["os", "s"], "filename": "3356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 11, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 2, "nloc": 9, "token_count": 53, "name": "operator < <", "long_name": "operator < <( ostream & os , const bitset<N> & bs)", "start_line": 80, "end_line": 88, "parameters": ["os", "bs"], "filename": "3356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 9, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 7, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 155, "name": "solve", "long_name": "solve()", "start_line": 105, "end_line": 129, "parameters": [], "filename": "3356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 25, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}, {"cyclomatic_complexity": 3, "nloc": 14, "token_count": 65, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 132, "end_line": 150, "parameters": [], "filename": "3356.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 19, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3357.cpp", "nloc": 22, "token_count": 158, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44006152", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 4, "nloc": 20, "token_count": 151, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 3, "end_line": 23, "parameters": [], "filename": "3357.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 21, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3358.cpp", "nloc": 32, "token_count": 183, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44005643", "exec_time": "46 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Specialist", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 0, "used_headers": 0, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 29, "token_count": 171, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 5, "end_line": 36, "parameters": [], "filename": "3358.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 32, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3359.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44005590", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Unrated,", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 6, "end_line": 29, "parameters": [], "filename": "3359.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 24, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "336.cpp", "nloc": 27, "token_count": 155, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/problem/B", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/279/submission/42883019", "exec_time": "312 ms", "memory": "800 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 1, "used_headers": 1, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 25, "token_count": 148, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 7, "end_line": 63, "parameters": [], "filename": "336.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 57, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]},
{"filename": "3360.cpp", "nloc": 26, "token_count": 221, "problem": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/problem/A", "solution": "https://www.codeforces.com/contest/1042/submission/44005501", "exec_time": "31 ms", "memory": "0 KB", "usertype": "Pupil", "function_count": 1, "library_count": 3, "used_headers": 2, "macro_count": 0, "function_details": [{"cyclomatic_complexity": 5, "nloc": 21, "token_count": 204, "name": "main", "long_name": "main()", "start_line": 11, "end_line": 57, "parameters": [], "filename": "3360.cpp", "top_nesting_level": 0, "length": 47, "fan_in": 0, "fan_out": 0, "general_fan_out": 0}]}]
